<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<feed xmlns='http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom' xmlns:blogger='http://schemas.google.com/blogger/2018'>
  <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665</id>
  <title>The Freedom To Move</title>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-464315984577968041</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>DRAFT</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Letter to my brother</title>
    <content type='html'>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is a shame that you and R will break up, she's a lovely girl. It is made even sorrier by your obsession with body shape.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Twice you have made your girlfriend's weight a sticking point, and before long we shall see that after both relationships the girl in question will become slimmer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What does it mean to you when your girlfriend puts on weight?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-12-12T23:56:24.830Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-12-12T23:56:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2011-12-12T23:56:24.836Z</updated>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-722286718089304402</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Playing In Church</title>
    <content type='html'>Today I played the piano at the Unitarian Church.  I was extremely nervous, and made some mistakes along the way, but my composition (I really need to give it a name) was well liked.

Feeling pretty good.  Nervous for Tuesday's job interview, but generally feeling in control.
</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-09-11T14:42:47.976Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-09-11T14:42:00.003Z</published>
    <updated>2011-09-11T14:42:47.981Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2011/09/playing-in-church.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-845746400474709450</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Semper Veritas</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>A Jol with JK</title>
    <content type='html'>Dear JK,&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
You are out of my league and I should not waste my time thinking about kissing you.&lt;br /&gt;
I am a full-time student, failed businessman, and have gone from job to job.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Actually, none of that is really relevant.&amp;nbsp; What matters is that, for all your friendliness, I get no sense that you like me as anything other than a friend.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
And then again, I find myself wondering.&amp;nbsp; The little glances, the shy smiles.&amp;nbsp; Do they mean anything?&amp;nbsp; Are you simply being hospitable?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I don't know.</content>
    <blogger:created>2013-07-06T16:33:09.690Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2013-07-06T16:38:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2013-07-06T16:38:13.485Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2013/07/a-jol-with-jk.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-1409841744390835887</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Semper Veritas</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Bad Dream: New Bed</title>
    <content type='html'>Last night I had a strange dream that I was really tired, because I hadn't been getting enough sleep.&amp;nbsp; (Which I haven't)&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
One evening, I found a new, plush bed in my room.&amp;nbsp; I slept in it.&amp;nbsp; But when I realised what had happened, Mum refused to take it out of my room.&amp;nbsp; (I prefer to sleep on the floor)&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Getting a new bed is actually a bad dream for me.&amp;nbsp; I think it represents loss of freedom. </content>
    <blogger:created>2013-04-29T20:50:08.570Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2013-04-29T20:50:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2013-04-29T20:50:08.578Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2013/04/bad-dream-new-bed.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-1444548729761827856</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>On Freedom and Liberty</title>
    <content type='html'>I don't want liberty, I want to be free: so I'll have to stay in here a little longer.

I feel better about moving back home.  The financial pressure is off me, I can see how I'm going to get out of this fix.  I also feel better for having made a decisive move.  My hand has been forced, but at least I'm playing it.
</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-09-01T15:29:46.853Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-09-01T15:29:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2011-09-01T15:29:46.909Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2011/09/on-freedom-and-liberty.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-1478786480452010810</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Moving Out And On</title>
    <content type='html'>In about a month from now I will move back home with my parents, and over the coming months I will prepare my application to study law.  That's the long and short of it.

I'm tired of swimming against the tide.  I have spent a decade going my own way, but I have gone as far down this path as I can go.
</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-08-28T13:08:11.388Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-08-28T13:08:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2011-08-28T13:08:11.421Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2011/08/moving-out-and-on.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-1497359796254005369</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Semper Veritas</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Conversations with Dad about Relationships</title>
    <content type='html'>I chatted to my father about online dating.&amp;nbsp; I told him that there weren't many girls online that I found especially interesting, but I'm happy to give it a go.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
He said that if, in his day, he had tried to find a wife through such a website, he probably would have never found Mum.&amp;nbsp; Although they have a few important things in common, they are very different in most of their interests.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I asked him what it was that made them realise that they wanted to get married.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
"Fools luck," he said.&amp;nbsp; "We were both young and naive, we didn't really know about these things, but we liked each other.&amp;nbsp; It's like going into a mining town as a prospector and coming out with a gold nugget.&amp;nbsp; But you realise this after the fact."&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
He went on to say that he reckons their being good friends for about a year before they became girlfriend and boyfriend helped a lot, and that the key is tolerance -- people are different, and you won't like everything, but if you're intolerant of the other's character it won't work.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
They being happily married since 1980, you can't argue with that.&amp;nbsp; That's my dad; he doesn't usually talk the talk, but he walks the walk.</content>
    <blogger:created>2012-08-03T06:49:06.707Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2012-08-03T06:55:00Z</published>
    <updated>2013-04-26T14:05:25.548Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2012/08/conversations-with-dad-about.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-1566623130863481698</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Lonely Friday Night</title>
    <content type='html'>It's 22:05 on a Friday night and I'm at home in bed.

I could call any number of people, but I'm too tired.

I had a crappy week on the job searching front, but there's a glimmer of hope -- an informal interview on Tuesday morning.

How do I feel about myself?  The other day when I went with Mum to a book launch, I realised that I, being casually dressed, would not be taken seriously at this formal event.  Likewise, I feel as if I don't have the right "clothes" to be taken seriously as an adult.  I haven't got a steady job, I'm down to my last couple hundred dollars, which will be gone on Thursday when my car payment is made automatically.  So when I speak to a 27-year-old, I feel as if I'm wearing cargo pants and a T-shirt and he's wearing a suit.  If I had the money for a suit it would be completely different, but in others' judgement I probably don't seem to have got my act together.

I miss being with someone, but I don't feel that I can take myself seriously.  I feel like a basket case.  Then again, once I've got a job and have been accepted into a law degree, I'll feel a lot better about myself.  But at the moment, if someone wants to know what I do, I have to talk in vague terms to try make my unemployment seem like general busyness.  Who wants to be with a 27-year-old whose career hasn't progressed in five years?  Then again, I've learned so much in the last five years, it really doesn't feel like a waste.  It just looks like it.
</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-09-09T12:18:29.805Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-09-09T12:18:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2011-09-09T12:18:29.811Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2011/09/lonely-friday-night.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-1868400929436507122</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Post- solital thoughts</title>
    <content type='html'>As I lay back, myself in my hand, the post-solital waves washing over me in a bed that need not have been empty, for the first time in a long time I thought, "I want to love again." But now is not the time for that. I have to be patient.</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-07-30T23:58:31.919Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-07-30T23:58:00.002Z</published>
    <updated>2011-07-31T05:45:21.479Z</updated>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='love'/>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='loneliness'/>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='work'/>
    <blogger:filename>/2011/07/post-solital-thoughts.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-1930839213158561934</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Running naked in a shopping centre</title>
    <content type='html'>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;I had a dream that I was lost in a shopping centre and as I ran around more and more frantically, looking for a way out to my car, my clothes came off article by article. First my top, then my trousers, then my shoes, my socks, and eventually I was streaking through the shopping centre with nothing but my underpants clutched in my fist desperately covering my genitals. I ran past a group of young women, who squealed in delighted scandal, and then chased me as I ran down a flight of stairs. As I bounded down the stairs I heard them laugh and and when I looked up I saw them removing their clothes too. Suddenly I realised that the my running was inciting my pursuit. I stopped and calmly put on my underpants. I watched them stop, saw their confusion and embarrassment, even though they were more clothed than I. I wasn't afraid, nor was I ashamed. In fact, I had forgotten why I was running in the first place. Then I woke up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content>
    <blogger:created>2012-03-28T08:53:09.432Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2012-03-28T08:53:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2012-03-28T08:53:27.168Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2012/03/running-naked-in-shopping-centre.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-2072326685030555986</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>DRAFT</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>What do I want to do with my life?</title>
    <content type='html'>This is a rough draft</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-10-09T21:33:32.642Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2013-04-26T14:06:00.002Z</published>
    <updated>2013-04-26T14:06:52.774Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2013/04/what-do-i-want-to-do-with-my-life.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-2076836168178833962</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>DRAFT</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Semper Veritas</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title></title>
    <content type='html'>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is to get a collection of Muslims to explain why different Sunnis and Shiites kill each other all over the world, and why Hudud is practised wherever there is Sharia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content>
    <blogger:created>2012-06-10T13:01:06.148Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2012-06-10T13:01:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2012-06-10T13:01:06.164Z</updated>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-2448024253896764042</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Semper Veritas</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Feelings before my exam</title>
    <content type='html'>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 45 minutes I'll commence my first exam and I feel woefully ill-prepared. When I look back on the last 14 weeks I have felt out of my element almost without cease. I did not understand how to make sense of this mass of information, and simply failed to find the right help. I have a tutor, but she can only guide those who are already on their way. Rather than apply myself as I know I can, I dispersed my energies in everything under the sun except for my studies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This term I wilted under a multitude of pressures. The talent I exercised was to reduce the expectations and commitments placed on me, rather than live up to them and fulfill them. It is frustrating in the extreme to know that I could do so much better, and have to endure four exams that will remind me viscerally of my failure to apply myself this term.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content>
    <blogger:created>2012-06-07T02:53:38.412Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2012-06-07T02:53:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2012-06-07T02:53:38.418Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2012/06/feelings-before-my-exam.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-2559842572808807122</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Hoping For The Best</title>
    <content type='html'>Last night my good friend DF helped me refine my CV, provided some feedback for my website, and gave me his thoughts on my cover letter.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Actually, he spent about an hour lambasting everything I had written.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I have been thinking for a while that there is something in what I do that intentionally (perhaps subsconsiously) antagonises those around me.  There were a few times that stick in my mind when I should have refrained from making a comment in Rachael's presence, but I went ahead anyway.  And I can't recall a particular instance, but I think I have a penchant for saying things that are the verbal equivalent of prodding someone.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I sometimes feel as if I'm on a course for catastrophe.  This problem of Uncle Michael's money is an obvious train wreck waiting to happen, but in a way, I have a sense that if it were not this it would be something else.  I feel as if I have invited life to beat me over the head with a stick, and now that it's obliging, I wish my problems would just go away.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I am bewildered to think that I could have wasted so much time worrying about my fling with SS when I had important work to do.  I spent accumulated hours SMSing her from the office, and not being focused on my work.  I am flabbergasted to think back on how complacent I was.  Then again, I was very, very bored by the work.  But then again, once I got into it, I started to enjoy it.  Why did I allow this opportunity to slip through my fingers?  Was I really so unhappy?  Did I really dislike it so much that I subconsciously sabotaged my best chance of coming through this ordeal?  I just don't get it.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I crave intimacy, but every time someone sets her sights on me, I feel like a complete charlatan.  "If you knew what a mess I have got myself into," I think to myself, "you would drop me faster than a bag of rats".  When shall I feel again that I can be with someone?  Certainly not until I've sorted this financial mess out.  And then, only if I am in a position to comfortably repay my debts.  Until then, I shall spurn every romantic advance.  I don't want to, but I shall.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I think I am carrying a bitter charge against the world, in a way blaming everything around me, not heeding anyone's advice, rushing headlong into my own plans until I run into a wall.  Then, as I fall back, reeling in pain, I cry out at the injustice that no-one was there to stop me from crashing.  But even if someone had offered to help, I would have ignored it.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Perhaps my bitterness stems from my not being in the right line of work, from not doing something sufficiently creative with sufficient autonomy.  There's some truth in that, but again, I could seek out creative work for myself within a role, I could acquire the right certifications.  If I weren't worried about my debt that is what I would do.  But right now, money over-rides all other considerations.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In a way it is convenient for me to have this huge problem: it means I have an excuse to put all other considerations on the backburner.  Maybe this is how I ultimately choose to live -- one problem at a time.  But that's no life, really, and some day I fear I shall tire of it.</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-08-09T22:49:41.186Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-08-09T22:49:00.002Z</published>
    <updated>2012-04-12T14:57:06.043Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2011/08/hoping-for-best.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-2568955378911200310</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Alexander Garber</name>
      <uri>https://plus.google.com/+AlexanderGarber1984</uri>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Thoughts about the Flirtation</title>
    <content type='html'>Dear P,&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
You sent me a friendly message on Wednesday a couple hours after we had gone our separate ways, but I did not feel like responding.&amp;nbsp; I was disappointed that what I thought was a sexual invitation was nothing of the sort and also having your friend come back home (after what came to pass with her) really killed my mood.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The thing that annoys me is not that you are uninterested (as far as I can tell), but rather that you flirted so heavily with me and gave rise to this misapprehension on my part.&amp;nbsp; For the last while you've been introducing highly sexual language into our conversations -- in light of recent interactions, maybe it is unintentional -- and conducted yourself in a way that made me quite certain that something was there.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
What I find now is that I don't really want to have much to do with you, even to the point of responding to your SMS.&amp;nbsp; You have become bothersome to me.&amp;nbsp; Having dealings with you reminds me of how foolish I felt on Wednesday to have given up the chance to work and make some much-needed money in favour of picnicking with someone who ultimately wasted my time.&amp;nbsp; I suppose I am a little angry at myself for making a bad decision; I only have myself to blame for it.&amp;nbsp; Even if we had made out, would that have really been what I wanted?&amp;nbsp; Not really.&amp;nbsp; I guess what I'm upset about is the fact that I feel so greatly the want of love and companionship that I knowingly made a foolish decision; a frustration that is aggravated by the embarrassment and disappointment of pursuing you sexually on the basis of a misapprehension of your interest.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
What I also find curious is that my sudden lack of interest in you seems to mirror how your ex-boyfriend treated you at the end of your relationship with him.&amp;nbsp; I wonder how many other men in your life suddenly lost interest in you and wanted to have nothing to do with you.&amp;nbsp; If this is a pattern, where did it come from?&amp;nbsp; Does it have something to do with your overt sexuality?&amp;nbsp; What is the significance of your anecdote that you convinced a group of friends to walk to the shops in their underwear?</content>
    <blogger:created>2014-02-06T21:57:15.025Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2014-02-06T22:11:00.002Z</published>
    <updated>2014-02-06T22:11:33.812Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2014/02/thoughts-about-flirtation.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-3075774711234053822</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Cheap talk</title>
    <content type='html'>When I talk about my life I often say the things I wish were true, not how things really are.</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-07-26T02:33:11.875Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-07-26T02:33:00.002Z</published>
    <updated>2011-07-31T05:45:51.290Z</updated>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='work'/>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='dreams'/>
    <blogger:filename>/2011/07/cheap-talk.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-3201788700416923191</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Steak Knives Salesman</title>
    <content type='html'>For the last hour and a half, I've been sitting at my computer, feeling as if I'm being slowly crushed by thoughts about money.

My libido is shot to pieces, my lower back is terribly tight, and I haven't the energy to do anything I'd like.  I'm not hungry, but I want to eat; I'm not horny, but I want to masturbate; I'm not interested in reading, but I want to record something on YouTube.  I do none of these things.

I have a glimmer of hope: a 100% commission based job selling kitchenware (steak knives etc.) in temporary stalls in supermarkets.  It promises the potential of earning enough money to pay my bills and save up almost enough to completely repay my debt.

Other thoughts I have entertained are of working as a truck driver in the mines or on an oil rig as a roustabout.

I also feel angry towards Alex and Rachael (stupid spelling anyway) for knifing me in the back.

Started to get tired now.  Said what I have to this evening.

Tomorrow is another day.  Off to the sexual health clinic to get tested again... Hooray.</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-08-03T13:50:28.200Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-08-03T13:50:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2011-08-03T13:50:28.282Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2011/08/steak-knives-salesman.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-3259986368814778006</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Money For Jam</title>
    <content type='html'>In a few minutes I expect Natalie will be here to deliver my order of jams for the office.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I have been preparing the sort of food that she likes -- I like it too.&lt;br /&gt;
I have been wondering lately whether sex with her was always as good as I remember it to be.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In one respect, I want her to make her delivery and be on her way; in another, I'd like her to stay.&amp;nbsp; It would be easy for her to stay.&amp;nbsp; It would be easy for me to let her stay over.</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-07-06T08:19:30.671Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-07-06T08:22:00Z</published>
    <updated>2011-07-06T08:22:15.940Z</updated>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='natalie'/>
    <blogger:filename>/2011/07/money-for-jam.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-3358942419705116476</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>DRAFT</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Work Tomorrow?</title>
    <content type='html'>Tomorrow I shall have a meeting with the boss.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I expect to find out the fate of my position at the company.</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-07-17T13:47:02.187Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2013-04-26T14:06:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2013-04-26T14:06:10.088Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2013/04/work-tomorrow.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-3423259709086335418</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>A Sad Dream of Pleasure</title>
    <content type='html'>This dream came to me in the space between slumber and rising.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I am rooted to the spot,&lt;br /&gt;
In a cavern;&lt;br /&gt;
All is white, shapeless, formless.&lt;br /&gt;
I can discern a door in the distance,&lt;br /&gt;
I think.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Where am I?&lt;br /&gt;
Why am I here?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I am naked, except for a pair of boxer shorts.&lt;br /&gt;
The air around me is warm and still;&lt;br /&gt;
Outside, the wind shrieks.&lt;br /&gt;
My feet are together,&lt;br /&gt;
My hands clasp each other behind my back.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I close my eyes and wait.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I feel the brush of soft fingers on my right thigh,&lt;br /&gt;
I keep my eyes closed;&lt;br /&gt;
I feel the brush of soft fingers on my left thigh,&lt;br /&gt;
I keep my eyes closed;&lt;br /&gt;
I feel an arm gently wrap my waist from the right,&lt;br /&gt;
I keep my eyes closed and extend my arms to my sides,&lt;br /&gt;
My hands are open, my palms face forward;&lt;br /&gt;
I feel an arm gently wrap my waist from the left.&lt;br /&gt;
Long finger nails stroke my outstretched right palm;&lt;br /&gt;
Long finger nails stroke my outstretched left palm.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I keep my eyes closed.&amp;nbsp; It feels good, but I don't want to give in to it.&lt;br /&gt;
Maybe if I keep my eyes closed I can pretend it is a dream.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The hands on my thighs slither between my legs,&lt;br /&gt;
And their arms wrap around my thighs,&lt;br /&gt;
Like vines around a branch;&lt;br /&gt;
My legs are separated;&lt;br /&gt;
I try to close them, but I can't.&lt;br /&gt;
Or maybe I could, but I don't want to.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The arms around my waist now fasten themselves and grip my hips.&lt;br /&gt;
The finger nails slide off my palms and my hands are clasped firmly.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I feel warm breath on my legs, on my chest, on my throat.&lt;br /&gt;
I smell perfume, and sweat, and desire,&lt;br /&gt;
The smell that prickles my nostrils just before we kiss.&lt;br /&gt;
Many pairs of lips hovering over me, brushing my skin.&lt;br /&gt;
Warm breath in my ears,&lt;br /&gt;
Hot breath on my lips,&lt;br /&gt;
The prickling smell is stronger,&lt;br /&gt;
I am getting harder.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
My legs are pulled farther apart,&lt;br /&gt;
My waist is being squeezed,&lt;br /&gt;
I want to pull my arms back in, but I can't,&lt;br /&gt;
Fingers start to pull at the fabric of my shorts.&lt;br /&gt;
I don't want to go as far as that,&lt;br /&gt;
Let's just keep it clean, I try to say,&lt;br /&gt;
But my lips are smothered by sweet, wet lips;&lt;br /&gt;
And it tastes good.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
My legs are stretched as far as they will go,&lt;br /&gt;
And yet the arms keep pulling;&lt;br /&gt;
My waist is being crushed, I can't breathe,&lt;br /&gt;
Maybe I don't want to breathe,&lt;br /&gt;
My breath is being stolen by a deep-tongued kiss;&lt;br /&gt;
My arms ache, nails dig into them.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I open my eyes and see them,&lt;br /&gt;
Beautiful and hungry,&lt;br /&gt;
All desiring me,&lt;br /&gt;
Why me?&lt;br /&gt;
What's so special about me?&lt;br /&gt;
What have I got to give that's so special?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I try to break free, but I can't move.&lt;br /&gt;
I try to keep my shorts on, to keep something between myself and them;&lt;br /&gt;
A hand unbuttons them and tears them off.&lt;br /&gt;
I am hard, very hard, but afraid too.&lt;br /&gt;
I try not to look in their eyes,&lt;br /&gt;
I don't want to have to pretend to smile.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I look up and away and wait for it to end.&lt;br /&gt;
I wanted anyway, I suppose, so why do I want to leave now?&lt;br /&gt;
I feel hands and lips as they enjoy me, pleasure me.&lt;br /&gt;
I comply -- how could I not? --&lt;br /&gt;
And wait for it to end.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Sweet sleep come to me&lt;br /&gt;
Underneath this tree&lt;br /&gt;
Do father mother weep?&lt;br /&gt;
Where does Lyca sleep?</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-07-17T13:45:13.074Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-07-17T13:46:00Z</published>
    <updated>2011-07-17T13:46:10.332Z</updated>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='dream'/>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='women'/>
    <blogger:filename>/2011/07/sad-dream-of-pleasure.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-3662047874013281940</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Alexander Garber</name>
      <uri>https://plus.google.com/108278368547579132111</uri>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Sex for Knowledge</title>
    <content type='html'>It has occurred to me that I have used sex, or at least the allure of sex, as a tool to get what I want from some women.&amp;nbsp; And what I want is knowledge.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
A combination of intellectual curiosity, expertise, erudition, and strong opinions in a woman, such that I become convinced that I could learn a great deal from her, is so fetching that I find myself willing to have sex with her, even if I find her to be physically dull or even slightly unattractive.&amp;nbsp; (If I find a woman to be hideous, no amount of intelligence or interesting character will overcome my repulsion, although I've been surprised by the extent to which my appraisal of a woman's attractiveness is subject to amendment)&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This probably sounds strange, coming from a man, so I should explain.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
At this curious stage of my life, many women find me attractive, but I'm not interested in anyone.&amp;nbsp; Although I have very little money, I am quite attractive (it has been made clear to me) and interesting, am very fit and in good shape, am intelligent, well educated, creative, well spoken, have a particularly pleasant voice (I am told ad infinitum), speak and write at a standard far beyond most people, have beautiful hair, can dance well, sing, play music, make videos, have a good sense of humour, etc. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Added to that, I am in the Goldilocks range -- young enough to be on the market, and mature enough to be a marriageable "prospect", and in a course of studies that promises financial stability upon graduation.&amp;nbsp; So I would say my market value is especially high these days, and will continue to rise for the next few years, I don't imagine this state of affairs will last forever. In addition to my perennial desire to love and be loved, I understand that the pool of women I would seriously commit myself to is rather small and will only get smaller: for the most marriageable women do not remain single very long.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;That's not to say there aren't women I am physically attracted to -- my heterosexuality is not in question, believe you me --, but I just can't seem to find anyone on my wavelength.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I think part of the reason is that I wield my intelligence as a filter.&amp;nbsp; When I realise that a girl whose intelligence has not impressed me is interested in me, I subject her to the most intellectually strenuous conversation I can muster (for example, the finer points of certain areas of economics that I am passionate about), in way, I suppose, to test her mettle.&amp;nbsp; Most women I do this to quickly lose interest, or feign interest.&amp;nbsp; But feigned interest cannot last.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
However, if I meet a woman who is bright, or erudite, or knowledgeable, or (especially) successful, then I become strongly attracted to her, even if I do not find her to be physically beautiful.&amp;nbsp; A few examples come to mind, but I'll use the current one, which is foremost in my mind.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I have started seeing a woman who is far too fat for my liking.&amp;nbsp; However, she is a very good prospect in every other respect -- intelligent, naturally pretty, a successful professional, sensible, not a feminist, votes right wing.&amp;nbsp; Moreover, she is someone that I could learn a lot from when it comes to working in the business world, and working as a professional in my chosen career path; in short, she's the sort of person I would happily have as a mentor in my professional life.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
We have kissed and engaged in some light sexual contact, and she said to me in no uncertain terms that she finds me very physically attractive, and if she were to lose about 15kg, I believe I would find her equally attractive.&amp;nbsp; I assume she won't slim down: every woman insists that she is working hard to lose weight, but in my experience a woman's talk about losing weight and keeping it off is nothing more than hot air.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Nevertheless, I feel that if I don't keep her sexually interested, I shall miss an opportunity to learn from her.&amp;nbsp; I couldn't resist her advances forever, and now that physical contact has been established, I can extract from her more of her experience and knowledge; however, this will inevitably be accompanied by her thoughts and feelings.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
It would be far more convenient for me to remain in the friendzone, because once I have exhausted her reserve of useful knowledge -- I always do -- I could stop seeing&amp;nbsp; her and move on to someone else.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
All of this worries me.&amp;nbsp; With this woman, I genuinely believe that I would be far more inclined to open up to her if she were slim, but I do not believe there is any way to tell her that I would prefer for her to lose a substantial amount of weight, without ruining my prospects of getting to know her.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
And so her weight serves as a useful excuse for me to shield my heart.&amp;nbsp; What confuses me is that I am not sure if my deliberations are a recognition that I'm simply not interested in her, or that I am interested in her and am afraid to admit it?</content>
    <blogger:created>2013-08-31T16:07:26.126Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2013-08-31T17:04:00Z</published>
    <updated>2013-08-31T17:10:48.457Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2013/09/sex-for-knowledge.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-3668637354084336672</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>DRAFT</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Alexander Garber</name>
      <uri>https://plus.google.com/+AlexanderGarber1984</uri>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>I Am Actually Angry</title>
    <content type='html'>I am angry at you.&amp;nbsp; Why?&lt;br /&gt;
I am angry at you for saying and doing things that made me feel safe enough to open up to you, and convinced me to fly to Thailand with you, and made me want to kiss you and have sex with you, only to then reveal to me that you are in fact only starting out on a journey of self-discovery and self-actualisation.&lt;br /&gt;
I am angry at you for making me feel so frustrated about physical affection with you.&amp;nbsp; It feels like a cruel trick, to make me desire you but to hold back.&amp;nbsp; No, that's not right.&amp;nbsp; You're keeping to the boundaries that we set.&amp;nbsp; Why do I want to keep on infringing these boundaries?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I am angry at you for making me believe that you had left the past behind and were ready to start a new chapter in life, only to &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I am angry at you for making me feel so aroused and scared, so cared for and rejected, so safe and threatened, so desirous of your affections and so distressed by your touch.&amp;nbsp; It angers me to think that if you kissed me and touched me, I would not resist your sexual overtures, even though I know I should.&amp;nbsp; I am frightened at how powerless you made me feel.</content>
    <blogger:created>2014-07-18T00:57:44.939Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2014-07-18T01:32:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-07-18T01:32:15.408Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2014/07/i-am-actually-angry.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-3913595534107083279</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Humble Pie</title>
    <content type='html'>I lost my job today.

After weeks of fretting, trying, worrying, trying again, and feeling that I got somewhere, Eugene the boss said, "I just don't think it's going to work out."

And that was that.

I believe that initially I sabotaged my prospects.

* I arrived late on the first day.
* I was very involved with Stav for a few weeks and SMSed her frequently during the day.
* I disappointed Alex by not coming over to his house to jam.
* I disagreed openly with Rachael about her feminism.
* I didn't take responsibility for my learning of the material.  I waited until Alex came up with something that worked.

There are other things, I'm sure.

The point is that all the things I did to shoot myself in the foot were not completely subconscious.  I was dimly aware of what I was doing, and yet I persisted until the situation demanded a change of tact.  Then, by the time I had convinced myself that this is what I wanted to do, it was too late -- no-one believed me anymore.

Maybe more on this tomorrow.
</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-08-01T13:45:24.632Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-08-01T13:45:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2011-08-01T13:45:24.684Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2011/08/humble-pie.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-4198750952727088574</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>DRAFT</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Letter to Josephine</title>
    <content type='html'>&lt;br&gt;I don't blame other people: they have their own stories and I'm just a side character in some of theirs.
</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-07-24T18:46:08.129Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-07-24T18:46:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2011-07-24T18:46:08.148Z</updated>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='None'/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-4657636741853382353</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Sunny Sunday</title>
    <content type='html'>It is Sunday afternoon, and I am about to head out to look at my brother's faulty computer.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I could arrange to meet Tessa, Stav, Josephine, Natalie, or Lisa, if I really wanted to; I don't really want to.&lt;br /&gt;
I'm also not in the mood to go swing dancing, even though Sarah would rather like me to be there.&lt;br /&gt;
Instead, I'm going to a meet-up of raw food enthusiasts, who are as far as I can see, a collection of middle-aged women who were probably hippies in their youth.&amp;nbsp; I'm unhappy with my weight, or rather my roundness.&amp;nbsp; More than that, I'm unhappy with feeling stiff and tired, inflexible and unfit.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I walked a few kilometres today and bought $20 worth of assorted nuts.&amp;nbsp; I'd like to see how far eating nuts, fruit, and vegetables will take me this week.&lt;br /&gt;
Along the way I spent some time in the park trying to do handstands and playing on the monkey bars.&amp;nbsp; It was fun.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I'm still very anxious about whether I'll lose my job.&amp;nbsp; I believe I have done enough to prove I'm worth keeping, but maybe they're just looking for an excuse to give me the boot.&amp;nbsp; Maybe all of this work I've put in has been for naught?&amp;nbsp; Maybe I've been deluding myself.&amp;nbsp; I want to disengage, lose interest, so it won't hurt, but I have to keep at it in the knowledge that I might suffer this crushing disappointment.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I have to stay focused, I have to hold my nerve.</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-07-31T05:44:02.496Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-07-31T05:44:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2011-07-31T05:44:02.532Z</updated>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='anxiety'/>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='work'/>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='women'/>
    <blogger:filename>/2011/07/sunny-sunday.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-4699695184530715262</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Failure</title>
    <content type='html'>&lt;br&gt;I have exactly three weeks to find another job. I can't believe I screwed this up. I can't believe I spent all that time thinking I was cruising when actually I was sinking. I was desperate to believe that I had it made; I ignored all the warning signs. Now I have three weeks before it will all come tumbling down.
&lt;br&gt;How could I let this happen?
&lt;br&gt;(Maybe this is just not the right job for me)
</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-07-18T04:51:27.543Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-07-18T04:51:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2011-07-18T04:51:27.760Z</updated>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='work'/>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='failure'/>
    <blogger:filename>/2011/07/failure.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-4728626366068447205</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Semper Veritas</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Sad Music</title>
    <content type='html'>The sad music plays, I close my eyes and feel the notes wash over me.&lt;br /&gt;
It's been years since I cried, years since I felt truly in love.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
It's always hardest late at night, when I've worked so much and there is still so much to do.&amp;nbsp; There's always so much to do.&amp;nbsp; My room is messy, my bed is empty.&amp;nbsp; My back is sore and my shoulders are tight.&amp;nbsp; My eyelids are heavy but I don't want to go to sleep.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I want to go outside, I want to run.&amp;nbsp; I want to get in the car, and drive drive drive.&amp;nbsp; Go somewhere far away, and when I get there, finally meet you.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I want to to meet someone to cry with.&amp;nbsp; I want to meet someone I can give my all to.&amp;nbsp; To be vulnerable with.&amp;nbsp; To let down my guard with.&amp;nbsp; To work hard for.&amp;nbsp; To build a life with.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Come to me, wherever you are.&amp;nbsp; Let me find you.&amp;nbsp; I'm here.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In peace I shall lay me down and sleep, for by your grace I shall dwell in safety.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Good night. </content>
    <blogger:created>2013-04-30T15:59:57.886Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2013-04-30T16:07:00.002Z</published>
    <updated>2013-04-30T16:07:57.896Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2013/05/sad-music.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-4741401006756428030</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Letter To Natalie, 18th July 2011</title>
    <content type='html'>Dear N,&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I have been thinking of you since your last visit.&lt;br /&gt;
I am afraid that you shall grow to hate me.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
It felt good to be with you, but it also felt wrong, like going running in the rain because you've been cooped up, in the knowledge that you'll get sick.  At the time it feels good, you feel invincible, the rain invigorates you.  But then you get home and unless you change out of your wet clothes you'll catch a cold.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Did I hurt you? Did I take advantage of you?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Maybe my occasional communications make it hard to forget me?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Do you still read the green book that I wrote you?  I can't imagine writing something like that for anyone else.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I was chatting to my friend JL and he was talking about having fallen deeply in love with someone from swing.&lt;br /&gt;
All I could feel at the time was bewilderment at his saying "we've fallen madly in love with each other" with a straight face.  Do people still say such things?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I wish I could love you the way I used to.  I wish I could love like that again.</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-07-18T13:01:52.676Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-07-18T13:01:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2013-04-26T14:09:49.951Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2011/07/letter-to-natalie-18th-july-2011.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-4858774134047837366</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>DRAFT</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Alexander Garber</name>
      <uri>https://plus.google.com/108278368547579132111</uri>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title></title>
    <content type='html'></content>
    <blogger:created>2013-08-31T16:01:13.252Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2013-08-31T16:01:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2013-08-31T16:01:13.255Z</updated>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-4870232095110470184</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Adjustments and Adjustments</title>
    <content type='html'>Last night N. came over, and she stayed the night.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I had wanted her to, she had wanted to.&amp;nbsp; She was attentive and warm and beautiful in her white shirt (slightly unbuttoned) and tights.&amp;nbsp; I avoided eye contact until she pointed out that I was doing so.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
We talked, or rather she invited me to talk about myself.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Eventually, our talk gave way to an embrace; our embrace, to kissing; kissing, ultimately to the bedroom.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
It felt comfortable and natural.&amp;nbsp; It felt easy.&amp;nbsp; Too easy, too comfortable.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
"Would you like some relief?" she asked at one point.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I wanted to say yes, I felt that I was slipping down a slope.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
She began to unbutton her shirt and then stopped.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
"What do you want?" she asked.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I refrained from replying.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
"What do you want?" she asked again.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
After a long pause, I said, "I want you."&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
She finished unbuttoning her shirt and I allowed my desire to take over.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
***&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I didn't get much sleep last night.&amp;nbsp; Apparently I was moving around a lot in my sleep.&amp;nbsp; I can't remember what I dreamed about, but I was upset by something.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I think I was already awake when my alarm rang at six in the morning.&amp;nbsp; I wanted to stay in bed with N.&amp;nbsp; but I had to get up, I had to get to work.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I didn't feel bad for having slept with N.&amp;nbsp; We didn't have sex, but we did other things, which are really a reminder of, a prelude to, a re-enactment of what we once had.&amp;nbsp; I didn't feel it would be the last time I'd see her.&amp;nbsp; I want to call her and talk about it, but what am I to say?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I got dressed quickly and she got out of bed too.&amp;nbsp; We hugged in the lift and I kissed her on the cheek -- quite a departure from last night, but last night felt like its own world.&amp;nbsp; I don't know how she feels.&amp;nbsp; I suspect she might feel rejected.&amp;nbsp; I still feature in her thoughts.&amp;nbsp; I don't think she wants to truly love someone else.&amp;nbsp; I'm not sure if I do either.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
***&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I'm afraid of losing my job.&amp;nbsp; I was called in for a meeting a couple of weeks ago, and pretty much told that I needed to shape up and work harder.&amp;nbsp; I've been trying hard.&lt;br /&gt;
Then last week the boss called me in and pretty much said the same thing, but also insinuated a couple of things that I don't think are fair.&amp;nbsp; But I can't say for sure whether he's wrong.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I don't feel I'm getting the benefit of the doubt.&amp;nbsp; I'm afraid that the people in my team want to see the back of me.&amp;nbsp; I feel that every day is a struggle against despair.&lt;br /&gt;
It's hard for me to feel that I'm not being unfairly criticised.&amp;nbsp; I fight against it, but I don't know if I'm struggling in vain.&amp;nbsp; I shan't know for a few weeks.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Dancing helps.&amp;nbsp; Exercise helps.&amp;nbsp; Sleep helps.&lt;br /&gt;
I don't get enough of any, partly because I'm worrying too much.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
If I do any more work then I'll be going to sleep late, again, but I haven't made up enough hours really.</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-07-07T10:39:08.350Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-07-07T11:07:00Z</published>
    <updated>2013-04-26T14:08:27.505Z</updated>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='stress'/>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='work'/>
    <blogger:filename>/2011/07/adjustments-and-adjustments.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-5049861325778500478</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Finances</title>
    <content type='html'>I have time to think things through, now that my uncle expects his money in May of next year.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Firstly, I have to see about getting another job -- whatever happens, I need that as soon as possible.&lt;br /&gt;
Secondly, I have to decide whether I want to pursue a career in IT.  Actually, I don't.  If anything, I want to pursue a career in making web videos.&lt;br /&gt;
Thirdly, I have to decide whether I want to study law.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In a way, the idea of studying law has always been there.  I narrowly missed out with my ENTER, and never really pursued it during my BA.  I gave it a sniff at the end of 2009, but that's as far as it's gone.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
If I do want to study law, I'll have to move back home.  No two ways about it.&lt;br /&gt;
Even if I saved up $40,000 in cash, that would not be sufficient for me to study full time and live here.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
But maybe that's the way for me to go.  Return here when I'm ready...  It doesn't seem as bad a prospect as it did 6 months ago.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Let's see how things progress on the job front though...</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-08-22T13:00:01.714Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-08-22T13:00:00.002Z</published>
    <updated>2012-04-12T14:58:06.382Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2011/08/finances.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-5282180908741797650</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Asking for it</title>
    <content type='html'>&lt;br&gt;I invite disaster;&lt;br&gt;
I court catastrophe;&lt;br&gt;
I flirt with failure,&lt;br&gt;
And when they come to me,&lt;br&gt;
I try to keep them at arm's length.
&lt;br&gt;But I find it hard to just say no.
&lt;br&gt;I'd like to like success;&lt;br&gt;
I don't mind some stability;&lt;br&gt;
I say hello to warmth;&lt;br&gt;
Rest and kindness too.&lt;br&gt;
But they will come and go.
&lt;br&gt;And when they do I'll give my other friends a call.&lt;br&gt;

</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-07-19T02:59:15.337Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-07-19T02:59:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2011-07-19T02:59:15.457Z</updated>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='depression'/>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='work'/>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='failure'/>
    <blogger:filename>/2011/07/asking-for-it.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-5345561691406637929</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>DRAFT</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Banking banking</title>
    <content type='html'>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;I feel switched on. About a year of living in fear is drawing tantalizingly to a close. I have to hold my nerve.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content>
    <blogger:created>2012-04-05T01:08:03.144Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2012-04-05T01:08:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2012-04-05T01:08:03.259Z</updated>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-5435716092546570673</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Gigolo Dream</title>
    <content type='html'>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;I dreamt that I prostituted myself and inconvenienced my friends. I had been paid before to make out with a woman and climax on her. I was driving a group of friends and we had stop across the road from the house where I had been paid before to do this and it occurred to me that this would be a good way to make a quick buck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I went in and was immediately assigned a middle aged woman who in her youth was probably very attractive. But her face was lined with years of stress and she had about her the nervous air of an insecure and needy teenage girl. I did what I had to do, and gave her good service, but everything seemed to take an eternity to complete. Eventually, we had got dressed and she didn't have enough money on her, so I was further delayed by waiting for her friend to produce the money, which was a piddling sum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I at last got out my friends were waiting around my car. Much of the good sunlight had been wasted, and I hadn't made nearly enough money to justify the inconvenience. I can't remember anything after that, all I know is I was embarrassed over what my friends knew about me and felt guilty for having ruined their day. I was in a bind of my own making and I couldn't immediately put it behind me. I would have to earn it back, bit by bit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content>
    <blogger:created>2012-03-31T21:19:21.852Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2012-03-31T21:19:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2012-03-31T21:19:21.981Z</updated>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='dreams'/>
    <blogger:filename>/2012/04/gigolo-dream.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-5548411862860363202</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Starting To Work</title>
    <content type='html'>Feeling a bit better.  Wrote a cover letter for what looks like a good job.
Any job that brings in the money is a good job at the moment.

Got a plan.  That's a start, right?
</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-08-06T16:40:28.562Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-08-06T16:40:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2011-08-06T16:40:28.651Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2011/08/starting-to-work.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-5589516913234733547</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Semper Veritas</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Early Night, Fitful Sleep</title>
    <content type='html'>This trimester at university, I should sleep in on Wednesdays, but after about four hours I found myself bleary eyed and feeling slightly nauseated.&amp;nbsp; I'm falling behind in my readings and starting to get very stressed.&amp;nbsp; If I keep this up, I'll get sick -- I can feel it coming on.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I'm almost recovered from my injury.&amp;nbsp; It'll be a long road back to the fitness and agility I enjoyed before my accident, but on the bright side I am considerably stronger in my upper body, and have been extremely productive in other respects.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I'd like to meet someone who exudes a certain kind of positive energy, who is a certain blend of pragmatic and idealistic; someone who understands me and wants the same things in life.</content>
    <blogger:created>2013-07-23T18:57:21.667Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2013-07-23T19:24:00Z</published>
    <updated>2013-07-23T19:24:11.327Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2013/07/early-night-fitful-sleep.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-5649646784666768768</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>DRAFT</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>When I clock out, I log out</title>
    <content type='html'>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just saying.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content>
    <blogger:created>2012-04-02T06:30:59.684Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2012-04-02T06:30:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2012-04-02T06:30:59.696Z</updated>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-6066686399643940550</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>DRAFT</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Semper Veritas</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Now And Then, Here And Now</title>
    <content type='html'>Once upon a time I lived in a place all of my own.&amp;nbsp; It wasn't a room, or a dorm, or a unit, or a flat, or even a house.&amp;nbsp; It wasn't a street or a neighbourhood, a hamlet or shire, a settlement or a village, a town, a station, a town, a city, a state, or even a country.&amp;nbsp; It didn't have a post code; it didn't even have a name.&lt;br /&gt;
But it was where I chose to live.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
What was it like?&amp;nbsp; Imagine waking up on a beautiful day in late spring or early summer, the warm, gentle sunlight pouring through your window, and you hop out of bed, look outside, and every colour is bright.&amp;nbsp; You pull on a pair of tracksuit pants and a T-shirt, and skip outside down to the park.&amp;nbsp; Along the way, a gentle breeze passes its fingers through your hair and the sunlight strokes your face.&amp;nbsp; When you get to the park, the grass is soft and the flowers are in full bloom.&amp;nbsp; You take off your shoes and run and skip and jump and flip.&amp;nbsp; A group of boys and girls are playing ball; you join in their laughing play on the green.&lt;br /&gt;
That's what it was like.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
And everyone was welcome there; it was as open as my heart.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Sometimes I ventured out from there, &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Once upon a time I used to live in my own place; not my own room, or unit, or dorm, or flat, or even my own house.&amp;nbsp; It wasn't my own street or neighbourhood, suburb or hamlet, village, town, sheep station, city, state, or country.&lt;br /&gt;
It didn't have a post code; it didn't even have a name.&lt;br /&gt;
But I loved there -- it was my primary residence, my main abode.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;It was as private as my thoughts and as big as my imagination, as happy as my dreams and as open as my heart.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Well, as open as it used to be.&amp;nbsp; It's not very open these days -- not the place where I used to live, mind, that's as open as ever.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
It's just... well, it's just I don't go there much anymore.&amp;nbsp; Don't get me wrong: it's still lovely; it's still everything it ever was, and will always be.&amp;nbsp; But I've changed, now that I think about it.&amp;nbsp; (I don't often think about it)&amp;nbsp; And besides, who has the time these days?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
You've got to live in this world, the here and now, stay focused, keep on achieving, stop dreaming.&lt;br /&gt;
Maybe not altogether, but don't overdo the dreaming bit -- make it work for you.&amp;nbsp; And when one dream comes true, find another one.&amp;nbsp; But don't be extreme with dreams; it's not normal; it's weird; people won't understand you.&lt;br /&gt;
You don't want to be weird, do you?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Where was I? Ah&amp;nbsp; yes, that place, where I used to spend all my time.&amp;nbsp; Great place to visit but there's nothing to do there, nothing but time and space to be yourself.&amp;nbsp; Boring!&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Anyway, must get back to work, got lots to do today.&amp;nbsp; I'll be glad when the weekend arrives.&amp;nbsp; I could do with a break.</content>
    <blogger:created>2013-05-04T16:34:31.006Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2013-05-05T15:35:00Z</published>
    <updated>2013-05-05T15:35:43.464Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2013/05/now-and-then-here-and-now.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-6094794627634082725</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title></title>
    <content type='html'>&lt;div style='clear: both; text-align: center; font-size: xx-small;'&gt;Published with Blogger-droid v2.0.4&lt;/div&gt;</content>
    <blogger:created>2012-02-07T17:32:33.957Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2012-02-07T17:32:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2012-02-07T17:32:33.975Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2012/02/published-with-blogger-droid-v2.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-6189376177622182885</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Semper Veritas</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Thinking Of A Girl I'll Likely Never Meet</title>
    <content type='html'>I've been thinking about the girl I met on the train on Thursday night.&amp;nbsp; Thoughts go through my mind -- "Did I write my number correctly?&amp;nbsp; Did she lose my number?&amp;nbsp; Why did she seem so friendly if she didn't want to get in touch?&amp;nbsp; Should I have asked her for her number?&amp;nbsp; Should I have asked her directly if she'd like to meet for coffee?"&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I feel silly thinking this at all.&amp;nbsp; Why should I be taken by a hi-bye girl?&lt;br /&gt;
Yes, she's very pretty; yes, she was writing out the conjugation of Greek verbs diligently in her notebook in neat, orderly handwriting... That is pretty exciting, I must admit.&amp;nbsp; I haven't met many pretty girls who do that.&amp;nbsp; I really admire that sort of diligence; I don't think you can be a dishonest person by nature if that's what you concentrate on during a train-ride home at 22:00.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I suppose time will pass and the memory of her will fade.&amp;nbsp; I'll focus on my goals, study, work, train, and keep moving.&amp;nbsp; For a while, I'll look at my phone occasionally, wistfully.&amp;nbsp; And then I'll forget about her.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I just have to be patient.</content>
    <blogger:created>2013-04-28T09:37:39.719Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2013-04-28T09:46:00.002Z</published>
    <updated>2013-04-28T10:06:53.189Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2013/04/thinking-of-girl-ill-likely-never-meet.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-6363498070311617429</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Scary Dreams</title>
    <content type='html'>I had two dreams:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In the first, Josephine declares her love for me, saying that she knew all along that I wanted her because I kept on seeing her.&amp;nbsp; I think marriage is mentioned.&amp;nbsp; I don't want a bar of it, but I don't know how to put the brakes on this.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In the second, I try pushing heavy weights in imitation of my father who tries to emulate some strong man.&amp;nbsp; After exerting myself at one point, my front three teeth (which were broken in my accident ten years ago) come loose and I pull them out.&lt;br /&gt;
My dentist wants to re-crown them and I'm not sure where I'll get the money for the procedure.&amp;nbsp; Also, my jaw has been very tight.</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-07-23T19:08:05.174Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-07-23T19:11:00Z</published>
    <updated>2011-07-23T19:11:17.575Z</updated>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='love'/>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='control'/>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='dream'/>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='fear'/>
    <blogger:filename>/2011/07/scary-dreams.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-6419053651763303590</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Thoughts on a Career</title>
    <content type='html'>Where do I want to be in 5 years, 10 years, etc?

At the heart of where I want to be is what I'd like to be doing.  Let's start with what I like and am interested in:

* Linux
* Ubuntu
* User Experience
* Software Development
* The legal issues around patents
* Discovering truth
* Communicating ideas
* Debating
* Helping people to realize their potential
* Leading a team
* Making a plan
* Managing a project

It's a start.
</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-10-10T01:46:06.049Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-10-10T01:46:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2011-10-10T01:46:06.093Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2011/10/thoughts-on-career.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-6471865941417249469</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Clockwork PC</name>
      <uri>http://clockworksausage.blogspot.com</uri>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>I Am Not Afraid</title>
    <content type='html'>I am not afraid.&amp;nbsp; I have been afraid, but I choose not to fear failure or rejection; this is a choice I shall have to make over and over again.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I am inspired by the poem Invictus, by William Ernest Hensley:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Out of the night that covers me&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Black as the pit from pole to pole&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;I thank whatever gods may be&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;For my unconquerable soul&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt; &lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;In the fell clutch of circumstance&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;I have not winced nor cried aloud&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Under the bludgeonings of chance&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;My head is bloodied but not bowed&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt; &lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Beyond this place of wrath and tears&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Looms but the horror of the shade&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;And yet the menace of the years&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Finds, and shall find, me unafraid&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt; &lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;It matters not how strait the gate&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;How charged with punishments the scroll&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;I am the master of my fate&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;I am the captain of my soul&lt;/i&gt;</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-07-05T12:47:46.722Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-07-05T12:47:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2011-07-05T12:56:23.119Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2011/07/i-am-not-afraid.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-6679565028081426391</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Rebuilding Clockwork PC</title>
    <content type='html'>Tonight is the first night in a while that I don't feel too bad about myself.

I went to the bank to enquire about a personal loan for $26,000.  Wow, $26,000 -- how did that happen?  How could I have spent so much money?  Well, I made practically no money from November until May, and my basic cost of living is around $3000 per month.  Then add to that all the expenses of moving in and various purchases... Well, it makes sense.  It's so much money.

If I take a 5-year loan, then it'll cost me about $282 per fortnight.  So every week, I'll have to find another $141 in order to service my debt.  Oh well, that's what I'll have to do.

My application will fail because I can't conceal from them that I just lost my job.  If I can get a job very soon, then I'll be able to go in at the end of November or early December having completed my probation.  It's leaving it to the wire, but if I can get into a job and do good work I'll be able to hold my nerve, I reckon.

So tired.  I hope I sleep well tonight.  Been going on too little sleep for a long time.

</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-08-08T13:21:11.391Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-08-08T13:21:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2011-08-08T13:21:11.419Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2011/08/rebuilding-clockwork-pc.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-6832203434177088786</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Playing With Fire</title>
    <content type='html'>You don't get it, do you?

It's not that I'm tired, or I'm having a bad day.
It's not that I've been working too hard.
It's not that I'm concentrating on something particularly absorbing.

You think I'm a good catch, you think you want to be with me, but you don't.
No-one in her right mind wants to really be with me.

What have I got to offer?

I'm worn out.
I'm tired.
Money's tight.

I dream of the day when I don't have to worry about repaying money, when I don't owe anyone.
I hate being in debt.

When you look at me you see something special, but what would the same images evoke in your brain if you know the contents of my thoughts?

You don't know me.  No-one does, really, and if you try to get too close, I'll send you out and slam the door behind you.

I want to feel free.  I'm tired of the feeling of marching through mud.
</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-07-17T16:23:16.661Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-07-17T16:23:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2011-07-17T16:23:16.744Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2011/07/playing-with-fire.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-7036473960700201857</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>New post</title>
    <content type='html'>/home/clockworkpcasus/Documents/Blogs/Feminism, My Enemy.txt</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-09-02T15:50:42.301Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-09-02T15:50:00.003Z</published>
    <updated>2011-09-02T15:50:42.308Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2011/09/new-post.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-7394872113934608935</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>I Have A Dream</title>
    <content type='html'>One day, when this nightmare is over, I'll say to myself, "I made mistakes, grave mistakes, but I emerged from the maws of despair resilient and better equipped to face the world."

I long for the day when I don't have a debt of $25,000 hanging over my head.  When I don't wake up at 05:14am breathing heavily, fretting about how I'm going to make ends meet, feeling that nothing I own is mine, feeling that everything I have is on the precipice of being taken away.  "If only I had not got myself into this mess," I tell myself, "I'd be happy and free, I'd enjoy a relationship without feeling that love for me cannot be real, because she doesn't know me, she can't be allowed to know me.  If she did, she certainly wouldn`t love me.  No-one truly loves a charlatan."

As my fingers walked cautiously through Arvo Prt`s "Variations for the Healing of Arinushka", I began to imagine myself beyond the confines of my situation, standing proud but not arrogant, at ease, unburdened, at peace.  As the notes climbed higher, I imagined myself in a position of privilege lending a hand to someone in a situation resembling my former state.  I`d say, "I made mistakes too, mistakes you couldn`t believe, but there is always something you can do.  Don`t give up; never give up."

I don`t want to give up, but sometimes I`m riveted by fear.  It poisons almost every meal and whispers taunts in my ear wherever I go.  Sometimes I liberate myself from it, for a little while, and I feel strong and free.  Yesterday I went to the park and overcame my fear of doing a handstand against the concrete wall.  I had put down mats but every time I tried to get into a handstand I pulled out.  I didn`t give up, I kept at it, again and again, until I got it.  A small victory, but a victory nonetheless.  Then it occurred to me that I`d really like to jump against the wall and put both feet on the wall before coming down: achieved with ease, first the right then the left, then left and right feet.  Now what about the fence?  Ran, jumped, right foot on with ease, left foot got stuck, fell on the concrete, didn`t get hurt.
Back to the wall, ran at it harder and faster, jumped higher and higher, feeling stronger.  Back to the fence, leapt over it with ease, came back round, leapt on to it, jumped off it; back to the mats, handstand again, push-ups from handstand, feeling stronger, feeling better, come down from the handstand, leap into the air, arm swinging in a punch to an invisible opponent, I can do this, I can do this, I can do this.
Leap on the wall, swing on to the stands, slide down the bannister, jump on to the fence, jump on to the grass; the grass feels good, do a roll, land on my feet.  I wonder if I can jump on to the fence and balance on it?  Jump, feet make contact, get the wobbles have to jump down.  Try again: jump, feet make contact, get the wobbles (slightly less this time), jump down.  Try again: jump, feet make contact, and there I am, crouching on the fence like a giant housecat, ready to leap, ready to sleep, I don`t care, I`m a cat and I`ll purr if I want to.

Jump down from the fence, wipe the sweat from my brow -- good sweat, honest sweat, sweat of success.
I could keep on going, but I don`t want to over-do it.  There`s always tomorrow.  It`s not as if I have a job to go to or anything like that.
Mustn`t think like that, have to stay up-beat.  Something will come along, there`s still time.  Don`t give up.

The music draws to a close, my fingers come to rest.  And for a few moments I am who I always wanted to be.</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-08-03T21:19:32.309Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-08-03T21:19:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2011-08-03T21:19:32.635Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2011/08/i-have-dream.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-7591559496482303980</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>DRAFT</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Little Boy Lost</title>
    <content type='html'>&lt;div&gt;
Blog Post: Saturday 9th July 2011&lt;br /&gt;
This morning when I awoke, the following image came to me.&lt;br /&gt;
I am rooted to the spot,&lt;br /&gt;
In a cavern;&lt;br /&gt;
All is white, shapeless, formless.&lt;br /&gt;
I can discern a door in the distance,&lt;br /&gt;
I think.&lt;br /&gt;
Where am I?&lt;br /&gt;
Why am I here?&lt;br /&gt;
I am naked, except for a pair of boxer shorts.&lt;br /&gt;
The air around me is warm and still;&lt;br /&gt;
Outside, the wind shrieks.&lt;br /&gt;
My feet are together],&lt;br /&gt;
My hands clasp each other behind my back.&lt;br /&gt;
I close my eyes and wait.&lt;br /&gt;
I feel the brush of soft fingers on my right thigh,&lt;br /&gt;
I keep my eyes closed;&lt;br /&gt;
I feel the brush of soft fingers on my left thigh,&lt;br /&gt;
I keep my eyes closed;&lt;br /&gt;
I feel an arm gently wrap my waist from the right,&lt;br /&gt;
I keep my eyes closed and extend my arms to my sides,&lt;br /&gt;
My hands are open, my palms face forward;&lt;br /&gt;
I feel an arm gently wrap my waist from the left.&lt;br /&gt;
Long finger nails stroke my outstretched right palm;&lt;br /&gt;
Long finger nails stroke my outstretched left palm.&lt;br /&gt;
I keep my eyes closed.&amp;nbsp; It feels good, but I don't want to give in to it.&lt;br /&gt;
Maybe if I keep my eyes closed I can pretend it is a dream.&lt;br /&gt;
The hands on my thighs slither between my legs,&lt;br /&gt;
And their arms wrap around my thighs,&lt;br /&gt;
Like vines around a branch;&lt;br /&gt;
My legs are separated;&lt;br /&gt;
I try to close them, but I can't.&lt;br /&gt;
Or maybe I could, but I don't want to.&lt;br /&gt;
The arms around my waist now fasten themselves and grip my hips.&lt;br /&gt;
The finger nails slide off my palms and my hands are clasped firmly.&lt;br /&gt;
I feel warm breath on my legs, on my chest, on my throat.&lt;br /&gt;
I smell perfume, and sweat, and desire,&lt;br /&gt;
The smell that prickles my nostrils just before we kiss.&lt;br /&gt;
Many pairs of lips hovering over me, brushing my skin.&lt;br /&gt;
Warm breath in my ears,&lt;br /&gt;
Hot breath on my lips,&lt;br /&gt;
The prickling smell is stronger,&lt;br /&gt;
I am getting harder.&lt;br /&gt;
My legs are pulled farther apart,&lt;br /&gt;
My waist is being squeezed,&lt;br /&gt;
I want to pull my arms back in, but I can't,&lt;br /&gt;
Fingers start to pull at the fabric of my shorts.&lt;br /&gt;
I don't want to go as far as that,&lt;br /&gt;
Let's just keep it clean, I try to say,&lt;br /&gt;
But my lips are smothered by sweet, wet lips;&lt;br /&gt;
And it tastes good.&lt;br /&gt;
My legs are stretched as far as they will go,&lt;br /&gt;
And yet the arms keep pulling;&lt;br /&gt;
My waist is being crushed, I can't breathe,&lt;br /&gt;
Maybe I don't want to breathe,&lt;br /&gt;
My breath is being stolen by a deep-tongued kiss;&lt;br /&gt;
My arms ache, nails dig into them.&lt;br /&gt;
I open my eyes and see them,&lt;br /&gt;
Beautiful and hungry,&lt;br /&gt;
All desiring me,&lt;br /&gt;
Why me?&lt;br /&gt;
What's so special about me?&lt;br /&gt;
What have I got to give that's so special?&lt;br /&gt;
I try to break free, but I can't move.&lt;br /&gt;
I try to keep my shorts on, to keep something between myself and them;&lt;br /&gt;
A hand unbuttons them and tears them off.&lt;br /&gt;
I am hard, very hard, but afraid too.&lt;br /&gt;
I try not to look in their eyes,&lt;br /&gt;
I don't want to have to pretend to smile.&lt;br /&gt;
I look up and away and wait for it to end.&lt;br /&gt;
I wanted anyway, I suppose, so why do I want to leave now?&lt;br /&gt;
I feel hands and lips as they enjoy me, pleasure me.&lt;br /&gt;
I comply -- how could I not? --&lt;br /&gt;
And wait for it to end.&lt;br /&gt;
Sweet sleep come to me&lt;br /&gt;
Underneath this tree&lt;br /&gt;
Do father mother weep?&lt;br /&gt;
Where does Lyca sleep?&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-07-09T05:39:51.466Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2013-04-26T14:06:00Z</published>
    <updated>2013-04-26T14:06:07.119Z</updated>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='dreams'/>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='sex'/>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='women'/>
    <blogger:filename>/2013/04/little-boy-lost.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-7950234585425120965</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Can't sleep</title>
    <content type='html'>Time is of the essence, I need to get to sleep.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Today my loan was finally approved and came through.&amp;nbsp; Tomorrow I'll transfer the money into my account and get it ready to transfer to my uncle at the end of May.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This saga will pretty much be over by June.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I've been watching a lot of videos on free market economics and libertarianism on YouTube.&amp;nbsp; The subject of liberty interests me intensely.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I subscribed to eHarmony for a month.&amp;nbsp; I'm not sure why.&amp;nbsp; I suppose it would be a convenient way of getting to know someone.&amp;nbsp; I've looked at the profiles of a few of my "matches" but they all seem to say the same thing, using the same language, expressing the same ideas.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Every night I lie in bed and think of someone that I've been with.&amp;nbsp; The memories of long-gone kisses revisit me frequently these days.&amp;nbsp; I don't really miss anyone of these women.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This weekend just past I attended Blues Before Sunrise.&amp;nbsp; It was fun to dance blues all weekend long, but I came away from it feeling a little empty.&amp;nbsp; I just didn't feel the excitement of being liberated by the dance; the girls (and a couple guys) who danced with me seemed to enjoy themselves, and I received many compliments, but the compliments seemed distant, or misplaced.&amp;nbsp; I didn't feel that I had managed to express what I wanted to express.</content>
    <blogger:created>2012-04-24T17:42:49.535Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2012-04-24T17:51:00Z</published>
    <updated>2012-04-24T17:51:23.715Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2012/04/cant-sleep.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-8124552977379621071</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Another Bad Night</title>
    <content type='html'>I got an email from my uncle that might buy me more time, but which could also lead to disaster.

He is under the impression that I opened a term deposit for 12 months with the bulk of his money, from which the terrible $26,000 are missing, rather than the 7-month term deposit that ends just after Christmas.  So it buys me more time.

However, he asked for the account number of the term deposit.  It's not in his name, so I don't believe he can check it, but if he can, then I'll be in huge trouble very soon. He also mentioned that the government has plans to tax the living daylights out of Whites in South Africa, which means that he might actually need these monies sooner rather than later.

I'm trying to take deep breaths and not panic.

The other problem that this presents is if I use his money as security, then I don't believe I can transfer it to the account in his name at his bank.  But once I've got all of that money together, it'll be a lot easier to work through that.

It weighs heavily on me.  I wish I could transfer all his money straight into his account.
</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-08-15T16:09:22.927Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-08-15T16:09:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2011-08-15T16:09:22.999Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2011/08/another-bad-night.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-8393979646436375762</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Semper Veritas</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Sometimes my heart aches</title>
    <content type='html'>It's been four years since I was in love, three years since I was in a serious relationship, and it's been a year since I decided that the next woman I sleep with should be the one I want to marry.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Most of the time I'm very happy.&amp;nbsp; It's a time of great energy in my life, tremendous movement, progress, creativity.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
But sometimes I feel (what do I feel?)... I feel the want of love.&amp;nbsp; Not romance, although that would be delightful.&amp;nbsp; Rather, the want of someone to hold and be held by; to kiss and be kissed by; to speak to and listen to; to laugh and cry with.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I chatted to a very pretty girl on the train last night.&amp;nbsp; I don't usually bother trying to talk with girls these days -- it all seems pretty silly to me now -- but she was leafing through a plain notebook, and in her notebook I spied columns of hand-written conjugated verbs in Greek.&amp;nbsp; She is Asian (Japanese, as I discovered), so it took me by surprise.&amp;nbsp; I struck up a conversation with her; she looked even prettier when she smiled.&amp;nbsp; I gave her my number and a link to my YouTube channel (she asked about it), so if she checks it out she'll see me doing all the creative things I like to do.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I guess I'm a little taken aback by how much I'd like to hear from her.&amp;nbsp; I guess really miss having someone in my life.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I have this recurring daydream...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;blockquote class="tr_bq"&gt;
We sink into a bed, in each other's arms.&amp;nbsp; Music blankets our bodies, the room is lit by moonlight.&amp;nbsp; Our hands claps and caress, we kiss and breathe each other's breath.&amp;nbsp; I enter you, and you take me in...&lt;br /&gt;
We climax together, and at the height of the exquisite pain, I allow myself to cry.&amp;nbsp; And I shower with you kisses as I water you with silent tears, and whisper I love you in your ears, and my hands take yours and yours take mine, and you wrap your legs around me, and I empty my heart in your presence.&amp;nbsp; And for a little while I allow myself to be weak with you before I go back to being strong.&lt;/blockquote&gt;
One day.&amp;nbsp; I just have to be patient.</content>
    <blogger:created>2013-04-26T14:12:52.860Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2013-04-26T14:28:00Z</published>
    <updated>2013-04-26T14:28:02.004Z</updated>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='love'/>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='romance'/>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='sadness'/>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='solitude'/>
    <blogger:filename>/2013/04/sometimes-my-heart-aches.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-8409461822315872964</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Alexander Garber</name>
      <uri>https://plus.google.com/+AlexanderGarber1984</uri>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Words will be had </title>
    <content type='html'>&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;This is what I am greeted by on a Saturday morning. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="separator" style="clear: both; text-align: center;"&gt; &lt;a href="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-y425L0VSs4g/VmspQJQi6cI/AAAAAAAAEBs/Hb_6YsC1jSQ/s1600/20151212_064809.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;"&gt; &lt;img border="0" src="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-y425L0VSs4g/VmspQJQi6cI/AAAAAAAAEBs/Hb_6YsC1jSQ/s640/20151212_064809.jpg"&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="separator" style="clear: both; text-align: center;"&gt; &lt;a href="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-mSTpByyH9-s/VmspRjV-r8I/AAAAAAAAEBw/MCmEKlWkatc/s1600/20151212_064806.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;"&gt; &lt;img border="0" src="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-mSTpByyH9-s/VmspRjV-r8I/AAAAAAAAEBw/MCmEKlWkatc/s640/20151212_064806.jpg"&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="separator" style="clear: both; text-align: center;"&gt; &lt;a href="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-OJ0KNssP6Co/VmspSjPrG1I/AAAAAAAAEB4/4ToOBbs66Ro/s1600/20151212_064802.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;"&gt; &lt;img border="0" src="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-OJ0KNssP6Co/VmspSjPrG1I/AAAAAAAAEB4/4ToOBbs66Ro/s640/20151212_064802.jpg"&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="separator" style="clear: both; text-align: center;"&gt; &lt;a href="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-5myvAv_2Tlg/VmspT7b0tRI/AAAAAAAAECA/FsG-KNwCJQE/s1600/20151212_064757.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;"&gt; &lt;img border="0" src="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-5myvAv_2Tlg/VmspT7b0tRI/AAAAAAAAECA/FsG-KNwCJQE/s640/20151212_064757.jpg"&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="separator" style="clear: both; text-align: center;"&gt; &lt;a href="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-Admn_Smwfe8/VmspUybcXkI/AAAAAAAAECE/WZw8OjmmVuM/s1600/20151212_064744.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;"&gt; &lt;img border="0" src="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-Admn_Smwfe8/VmspUybcXkI/AAAAAAAAECE/WZw8OjmmVuM/s640/20151212_064744.jpg"&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/div&gt;</content>
    <blogger:created>2015-12-11T19:51:48.816Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2015-12-11T19:51:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2015-12-11T19:51:48.832Z</updated>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='dispute resolution'/>
    <blogger:filename>/2015/12/words-will-be-had.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-8434893016874288007</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Stay Of Execution</title>
    <content type='html'>I spoke to my uncle last night.  He is under the impression that I put his money into a 12-month term deposit, rather than a 6-month one, which buy me some much needed time.  I have breathing space.
It's strange to me that the expression "breathing space" is now so visceral to me; I have been feeling for a long time that I am being strangled.  I still feel a suffocating guilt.

I have been thinking about where I'd like to go in my career.

Here are a few ideas of what I want from a job:

1) Creativity
2) Intellectual stimulation
3) Autonomy and guidance
4) Freedom of movement
5) Freedom of thought
6) Flexible work time
7) No dress gode

I'm getting fitter and trimmer.  That feels good at least.

Been drinking my beer; tired.

Good night.
</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-08-18T15:33:14.031Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-08-18T15:33:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2011-08-18T15:33:14.124Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2011/08/stay-of-execution.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-8522847177072020822</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Two Good Days In A Row</title>
    <content type='html'>Things might be turning around at work.  It felt good to answer tricky questions today -- I feel that I've turned a corner.&lt;br /&gt;
Not afraid of the work so much, not shirking work.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
My libido is down, down, down. Right now it's just not interesting to me.&lt;br /&gt;
I don't feel bad about having slept with anyone, but at this point I can't even picture myself doing it.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I guess what I'm conveying to JC is that I'm not rejecting her per se, but that she has no place in my life until the work situation is stable.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I did the same when I was seeing KG and I worked at FS.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I see any girl in my life as a threat to the stability of my existence.  I enjoy the chatting, the flirting (to some extent), but not a relationship unless it's completely according to my timetable.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Too tired to think about it now.</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-07-20T13:53:14.312Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-07-20T13:53:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2013-04-26T14:10:25.770Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2011/07/two-good-days-in-row.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-8883298615577541117</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>An Honest Letter</title>
    <content type='html'>*************&lt;br /&gt;
Josie's Email&lt;br /&gt;
*************&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Dear Alex,&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I have been brooding about writing this letter for over a week, but now that I'm here, sitting, and actually writing, the anger I felt while thinking has congealed into sadness.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I realize that this is a difficult time for you, but nonetheless I do feel used and hurt as both a friend and a lover.&amp;nbsp; It's as if that during the birth of our relationship I was not really a perspective friend but merely an audience for you at your convenience. You talked incessantly about yourself, you never endingly quoted your poetry without showing believable indication of interest in mine, you laid out your opinions and knowledge before me like a lecture, but hardly ever did you give me breath to mention myself. And when I did, I was so exhausted listening that my mind was numbed--as if you demanded a dental patient shot up with Novocaine to perform a soliloquy or aria.&amp;nbsp; But somehow, unless it was about your love of computers, even my rare spotlight shifted onto you.&amp;nbsp; Perhaps not calling me on or near my birthday caused me to snap.&amp;nbsp; After countless hours on the phone listening to you, giving you my time, you failed to give me a moment on my one special day.&amp;nbsp; As a lover, I feel doubly used. What was that about, really? Was I just another vagina to conquer? You chased me hard and persistently.&amp;nbsp; You got me. You fucked me. And then, like a good jerk, disappeared.&amp;nbsp; If you no longer desire for that relationship to continue, then you could have at least given me the courtesy to say so.&amp;nbsp; You've blundered in this new, budding friendship, and the next couple of moves will determine the rest of the game.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Peace,&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Josephine&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
*********&lt;br /&gt;
My Reply&lt;br /&gt;
*********&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Dear Josie,&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I agree with much of what you wrote.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I really am very sorry.&amp;nbsp; You deserve better.&lt;br /&gt;
You have been treated shabbily and I should have been more honest with you.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I do, however, bristle at the accusation that I used you, especially the implication of callousness.&amp;nbsp; You certainly were not a mere conquest for me, even if from the outside that seems to be the case.&amp;nbsp; It was not as simple as this sequence of events:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
"You got me. You fucked me. And then, like a good jerk, disappeared."&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Part of me wanted to continue seeing you, part of me -- the stronger part -- wanted to be alone.&amp;nbsp; You weren't another "vagina to conquer" by any stretch of the imagination.&amp;nbsp; That's not who I am, and quite frankly nothing is further from my mind right now than finding someone to be with.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Having said that, what happened in actuality did hurt you, and I won't try to diminish the importance of your hurt.&amp;nbsp; Whatever my motivations, there was no reason to withdraw inexplicably from your affections.&amp;nbsp; I could have, should have been more upfront with you.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
So why did I blunder in this budding friendship?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Simply put, I want to be alone.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Not because of anything you did or said, not because I wanted to inflict anything on you, but simply because I'm in a deep, deep well and I have neither the means nor the will to emerge from it.&lt;br /&gt;
In my cowardice, I never found the right time or place or way to convey this to you other than through inaction and lack of communication.&amp;nbsp; Failure to do so was precisely that -- a failure on my part.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Further to this, it's facile to blame my blunder on the current difficulties in my life: they can just as easily be an opportunity to open my heart. &lt;br /&gt;
But I don't want to open my heart.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
You don't deserve to be saddled with all of this: these aren't your problems.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I'd like us to be friends, but friendship is a matter of give and take, and you are quite right that I've been taking a lot more than I've been giving. &lt;br /&gt;
I just don't have much to give at the moment and everything else in my life pales into insignificance alongside the problems I need to solve with increasing urgency.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This is admittedly not a recipe for happiness, but I don't want to be happy right now.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I'm sorry for the pessimism and negativity of my reply.&amp;nbsp; It's honest though.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
If I were you, I would give myself a wide berth for the next couple of months.&amp;nbsp; I'd be saddened terribly if you should grow to despise me, and the more you have to do with me at the moment, the more likely this will be, I'm afraid.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Peace,&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Alex</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-08-24T14:25:37.730Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-08-24T14:25:00.004Z</published>
    <updated>2011-08-24T14:25:50.832Z</updated>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='love'/>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='loneliness'/>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665' term='women'/>
    <blogger:filename>/2011/08/honest-letter.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-8925144760097671338</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>The Desire for Control</title>
    <content type='html'>The desire to be in control of my life is a key theme in my story.&amp;nbsp; It's not that I want to be in control of everything or everyone around me, but I absolutely detest feeling overwhelmed by someone else or by my circumstances.&amp;nbsp; As long as I'm the captain of my own boat I don't mind if the sea gets choppy or if others get to pilot ships.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Last year, during a blues dancing festival, I was much in demand as a lead.&amp;nbsp; I was, of course, very happy about this, but something impinged on my enjoyment greatly.&amp;nbsp; There were a couple of girls with whom I am on good terms who kept on placing themselves in a position where I felt obliged to dance with them.&amp;nbsp; I am at my happiest when I can flutter from girl to girl on the dance floor and not feel obligated to dance with anyone.&amp;nbsp; I want to enjoy the sense of adventure and not have to make considerations of whom I feel obligated to dance with.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Have lots to do tomorrow.&amp;nbsp; Always lots to do.&amp;nbsp; It would be nice to get away for a bit, but I don't see that happening...</content>
    <blogger:created>2012-04-12T15:08:59.269Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2012-04-12T15:18:00Z</published>
    <updated>2012-04-12T15:18:53.888Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2012/04/desire-for-control.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-8952464546688857490</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Feminism, my arch enemy</title>
    <content type='html'>&lt;div&gt;Wherever I come across a girl who is sympathetic to feminist theory, I am moved by a great urge to argue about feminist theory with her. It's a pointless argument, and it predictably upsets her, but once I get going I can't help myself; I am impelled to argue point after point until the argument is exhausted.&lt;br /&gt;
Why does feminism offend me so? I see it as a pernicious ideology that warps a girl's reason and exploits powerful emotions that she carries.&lt;br /&gt;
The least likely way of convincing a feminist of this is by arguing with her about it. I'm not really arguing with the person in front of me, in a way she's just the representative of someone else.&amp;nbsp; What does winning such an argument represent? It doesn't change anything; I don't hope to achieve anything.&lt;br /&gt;
Maybe it's the years of feeling isolated and derided at university. Maybe it's the anger at rarely being able to take on those who caused me hurt at the time, feeling powerless. Maybe it's the anger, the resentment at watching the years in my degree flushed down a toilet of intellectual dishonesty? Maybe it's the embarrassment of going through a degree in which I was subjected to years of hogwash? I suppose I still feel terribly bitter about being robbed of an education in the liberal arts - so much unhappiness, feeling so alienated from academia.&lt;br /&gt;
And all of the blame for this I can lay at the feet of the influence of feminism on my studies and the girls around me, perfectly decent girls who were given easy answers that men are to blame for how they feel about themselves.&lt;br /&gt;
I suppose I feel impelled to fight back, to turn today's conversation into yesterday's battle ground.&lt;/div&gt;</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-09-02T15:50:23.742Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-09-02T15:50:00.004Z</published>
    <updated>2012-04-12T14:59:48.492Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2011/09/feminism-my-arch-enemy.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5842320223498240665.post-9057557626868685854</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Natty Narwhal</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>New post</title>
    <content type='html'>hello</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-09-11T14:42:32.750Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-09-11T14:42:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2011-09-11T14:42:32.755Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2011/09/new-post_12.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
</feed>