<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<feed xmlns='http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom' xmlns:blogger='http://schemas.google.com/blogger/2018'>
  <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4445927532978913051</id>
  <title>CajunTechie's Mindstream</title>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4445927532978913051.post-6893444890584935631</id>
    <blogger:parent>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4445927532978913051.post-3252811881020841312</blogger:parent>
    <blogger:type>COMMENT</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Clockwork PC</name>
      <uri>http://clockworksausage.blogspot.com</uri>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title></title>
    <content type='html'>As a passionate supporter of FOSS in all shapes and sizes, I decided to put my money where my mouth is and actually sell computers that dual-boot and personally provide technical support to new users.  I also encourage non-Linux users to use LibreOffice and Firefox, etc. Unfortunately, if someone doesn&amp;#39;t mind spending loads of money, there isn&amp;#39;t a single packaged rival to Apple&amp;#39;s user experience -- not to say there couldn&amp;#39;t be, there just isn&amp;#39;t.  By this I mean from the moment you walk into an Apple store (there is no &amp;quot;Ubuntu&amp;quot; store, although there should be), to the user interface, to the technical support at the so-called Genius Bar, Apple users are irritatingly proud of being so.  And a HUGE component is Apple&amp;#39;s careful attention to &lt;b&gt;DESIGN&lt;/b&gt;.  Personally, I think Apple&amp;#39;s design is limiting and a little cold, but at least it&amp;#39;s consistent and it evidently appeals to lots of people.  And Apple achieved this with experts and *some* user feedback.  Apple&amp;#39;s goal was to attract disgruntled Windows users, and what do you know?  It actually worked.  Mark Shuttleworth is unfairly lambasted on blogs like this one for staring reality in the face and not blinking.  If we want Ubuntu to be the preserve of tinkerers, then no change is needed, but Ubuntu was NEVER intended to be yet another community distro -- its aim was always at the mainstream.  And I find it ironic that the same Linux users who are so open to change in almost every other respect behave like the most childish M$ Windows users as soon as very important, well thought out changes to the UI are introduced.  There won&amp;#39;t be a mass exodus from Ubuntu, because it strikes the best balance between the needs of experts and novices.  If you want to get your hands dirty, do so by all means with Gentoo or Arch or even Fedora (which you can bet will be crash prone), if 11.04 isn&amp;#39;t to your liking then OK stick with 10.04 or 10.10 if you must.  But stop whining about not being heard.  There are millions of Ubuntu users: we can&amp;#39;t all be listened to.</content>
    <blogger:created>2011-04-24T03:09:21.502Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2011-04-24T03:09:21.502Z</published>
    <updated>2011-04-24T03:09:21.502Z</updated>
  </entry>
</feed>