<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<feed xmlns='http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom' xmlns:blogger='http://schemas.google.com/blogger/2018'>
  <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-6380399819551683294</id>
  <title>My Journal</title>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-6380399819551683294.post-1007935621197043345</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>clockworksausage</name>
      <uri>http://www.clockworksausage.com</uri>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>I hate driving</title>
    <content type='html'>Today I spent about four hours in heavy traffic. &amp;nbsp;I had looked forward to a nice relaxing Sunday; instead, I got to drive to Oakleigh for some quick shopping -- very necessary but not relaxing -- before getting back into the car for a drive to Spencer Street station. &amp;nbsp;The drive there wasn't too bad, but since we missed her train, I decided to go to the swap meet to buy RAM. &amp;nbsp;You'd think from Spencer Street to Hoddle Street on a Sunday afternoon wouldn't be too bad, but it could have been 08:30 on Monday from the way the traffic was crawling.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Then on the way back to Spencer Street there was an almighty traffic jam that almost caused us to miss the next train; luckily I sped around the Telstra Dome and got her there in the nick of time. &amp;nbsp;Then the fun really began: I couldn't bear the thought of re-entering the city, so I decided to go via St Kilda. &amp;nbsp;Only today was the St Kilda festival and by the time I got down there, sweating from frustration, I came to realise that all the roads on that side of the river were blocked! &amp;nbsp;So I had to crawl back into the city in bumper-to-bumper traffic until I could drive into Albert Park -- on a Sunday afternoon -- which turned out faster than the main roads. &amp;nbsp;By the time I got back home my back was sore and my day buggered. &amp;nbsp;Then I got a call from her announcing she was coming back into the city and then to Murrumbeena to retrieve her present. &amp;nbsp;Only her stupid car's radiator is kapput, so I had to go out to lend her a hand. &amp;nbsp;So back into my poor little car, back into the city, to keep her company while she tried to pour water into her car's leaky radiator. &amp;nbsp;As I snuck into a nearby hotel's toilets in order to fill up her water bottles, I thought to myself I don't need this shit.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I really wonder sometimes what I'm doing with her. &amp;nbsp;I just wish her mother were dead so that her life, no scrap that, my life, my life with her could be at least halfway normal. &amp;nbsp;I don't wish her mother a painful death, on the contrary, a peaceful one, in her sleep, surrounded by her loved ones, so that no-one would be to blame. &amp;nbsp;The best thing that could come of her accident is the determination of Natalie's character, which has already come to pass; now all her mother does is keep her bound to her useless father. &amp;nbsp;I really find it hard to believe she's really thirty.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I'm sick of having my life weighted by her basket-case family. &amp;nbsp;I want something normal with her, not some bloody sob story. &amp;nbsp;On some days it's really all too much for me.</content>
    <blogger:created>2010-02-14T16:10:32.358Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2010-02-14T16:23:00Z</published>
    <updated>2010-02-14T16:23:16.818Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2010/02/i-hate-driving.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-6380399819551683294.post-2638427082507178928</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>DRAFT</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Clockwork PC</name>
      <uri>http://clockworksausage.blogspot.com</uri>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Green Screen Recording</title>
    <content type='html'></content>
    <blogger:created>2010-12-13T13:00:00.766Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2010-12-13T13:00:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2010-12-13T13:00:00.772Z</updated>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-6380399819551683294.post-2863447401667483181</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>DRAFT</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Clockwork PC</name>
      <uri>http://clockworksausage.blogspot.com</uri>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Green Screen Recording</title>
    <content type='html'>Best Settings&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Both lights on.&lt;br /&gt;
Camera zoomed in half way.&lt;br /&gt;
Shutter priority TV&lt;br /&gt;
White balance Auto</content>
    <blogger:created>2010-12-13T05:16:13.458Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2010-12-13T05:16:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2010-12-13T05:17:29.980Z</updated>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-6380399819551683294.post-3107930400862316035</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>aMapMapper</name>
      <uri>http://www.clockworksausage.com</uri>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Conflation of Love and Love's Stress</title>
    <content type='html'>As I lie in bed, trying to pleasure myself to sleep, I realise that thinking of her does not excite me anymore.  I think of someone else, and I become excited.  Someone else would be so refreshing, so new, so far removed from the weary, heavy, complicated feelings I wrestle with every day.&lt;div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;She is still beautiful in my eyes, but I cannot dance with her; I love the way she feels, but her words fall flat on my ears; I admire her adaptability, but still resent the guilt that her willingness to go along with things ultimately brought about in me.  I can't blame her, but I still resent the way she, or perhaps her situation, or perhaps she and her situation, made me feel.  And my desire for her is more by force of habit, I feel, than by genuine excitement.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;At the same time, we've come a long way.  We have something special.  But I find myself wondering whether there might be someone out there for me with whom life would not be so difficult.  And then I feel guilty for considering the possibility.  And then I feel angry for being made to feel guilty.  And then I feel, well, just confused; I hit a wall, turn back, and forget why I made the trek in the first place.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;I feel inclined to pass judgement.  Passing judgement makes me feel strong and safe: it's something I can do.  Even if I can't solve something, I can still point out what's wrong with it; &lt;i&gt;&lt;span class="Apple-style-span"  style="color:#99FF99;"&gt;if she had been more inclined to do the same, she wouldn't have been in this mess&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;.  Really?  I don't think so.  The truth is her father had her over a barrel and the moment he came into all that money, he was geared to lose it one way or another.  He drove his own father into the poor house, why not his wife and daughter?  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span class="Apple-style-span"  style="color:#99FF99;"&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span class="Apple-style-span"  style="color:#99FF99;"&gt;Well, she should just get herself the hell out of there.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Look, we've been through this already.  If she wrenches herself from her mother, and then discovers that harm has come to her mother in her absence, there will be no relationship.  Her sense of self will be obliterated and all the years of frustration will well up, and I'll be the only one in sight to direct it at.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span class="Apple-style-span"  style="color:#99FF99;"&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span class="Apple-style-span"  style="color:#99FF99;"&gt;OK, so you leave her.  Leave her to her good-for-nothing father and her mother; let her grow old caring for someone whose life simply drags everyone else's into poverty.  Let her remain a kind of overgrown infant until her mother passes away some twenty years from now: she'll take over an orphanage or a start a sanctuary for cats or something.  It's not your problem.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;But I don't want to leave her.  I love her; I don't want to find someone else; I want to work something out.  It's not right to abandon someone for trying to do good.  She could be such a good partner, wife, mother, businesswoman... if she could just leave home and not have to care for her helpless mother and self-destructive father.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span class="Apple-style-span"  style="color:#99FF99;"&gt;But she won't, will she?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;No, I suppose not.&lt;/div&gt;</content>
    <blogger:created>2010-02-02T13:13:07.437Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2010-02-02T13:12:00Z</published>
    <updated>2010-02-02T13:33:35.369Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2010/02/conflation-of-love-and-loves-stress.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-6380399819551683294.post-3511415139886346068</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>clockworksausage</name>
      <uri>http://www.clockworksausage.com</uri>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Queasy Tummy</title>
    <content type='html'>I'm going to both an acupuncturist and a shiatsu therapist;  I also see a psychologist: I have a lot of anger.

I didn't realise I carry so much anger, but I do.

Yesterday my shiatsu session consisted in a reiki treatment.  As her hands passed over my body my mind drifted in and out of images and thoughts; at certain points she felt a violent blockage of energy and concentrated on them until the energy burst through like a river breaking its dam.  During those periods my mind was filled with dark, angry thoughts, as if I had driven into a thick fog, not knowing when I might emerge from it and always emerging so suddenly and so easily that it was hard to believe I had thought those things; in fact, after a few moments the very thoughts themselves had dissipated.</content>
    <blogger:created>2010-02-03T14:31:10.949Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2010-02-03T14:30:00Z</published>
    <updated>2010-02-03T15:18:25.449Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2010/02/queasy-tummy.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-6380399819551683294.post-6849701299650928363</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>clockworksausage</name>
      <uri>http://www.clockworksausage.com</uri>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Post-Blues Blues</title>
    <content type='html'>Daniel,&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I am extremely reluctant to take you to blues dancing again because I am terrified that you will ruin my reputation.&amp;nbsp; I don't think you are mature enough to earn a good reputation on the Swing Patrol; what's more, my association with you means that your belligerence will bring me into disrepute.&amp;nbsp; When we're at home you talk ad nauseum about women like some trashy, misogynistic, sleazy wog and you at the blues night you were talking with that fake cockiness that you have obviously picked up from your low-life friends.&amp;nbsp; I invited you along because I know that you're unhappy and tired of the same old rounds with your friends; I hoped you would enjoy the blues dancing; however, I didn't realise how dangerously immature you are on that scene.&amp;nbsp; It has taken me a good year of attending classes, fretting, practising, trying, learning, suffering from anxiety, and trying very hard in order to feel comfortable when I go dancing.&amp;nbsp; I would much rather prefer that something else take your fancy, so that I can go without fear of your doing anything that would besmirch my good name.</content>
    <blogger:created>2010-03-08T14:50:12.095Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2010-03-08T14:57:00Z</published>
    <updated>2010-03-08T14:57:31.805Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2010/03/post-blues-blues.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-6380399819551683294.post-7086168275978993797</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>clockworksausage</name>
      <uri>http://www.clockworksausage.com</uri>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Low Libido</title>
    <content type='html'>Well, that's exactly it.&amp;nbsp; My libido is low, and it has been for quite a while.&amp;nbsp; In fact, I haven't really enjoyed sex, that is, I haven't made love to Natalie for a long time.&amp;nbsp; At first, we made love, and there was a great bond between us; it was a dance, an escape, to be immersed in without thinking about it.&amp;nbsp; It felt natural and caring; it was fun.&amp;nbsp; Natalie was my personal embodiment of feminine beauty, my living fantasy.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
At some point it stopped being fun.&amp;nbsp; Worries, irritations, and all manner of bad thoughts began to invade my mind during our love-making.&amp;nbsp; I went through a period of fantasising about other girls; I dreamt of sleeping with other girls -- the dreams were never filled with desire -- I never lusted for another girl -- but Natalie had ceased to be the embodiment of my desire.&amp;nbsp; My sexual urges were still there and I continued to perform, but I was either going through the motions or taking out my frustration in the form of vigorous sex -- no longer love-making, but rather energetic sex.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
To a great extent the constant failure of my working life has contributed to my being unceasingly anxious.&amp;nbsp; I feel like a failure, for instead of earning good money in a respectable job, I scrounge around for work and feel that I'm always running out of money.&amp;nbsp; I feel overwhelmed a lot of the time.&amp;nbsp; Small setbacks can ruin my mood for the day and send me flying into an intellectually absorbing activity to escape it.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Much as I am loathe to admit it, I resent Natalie for staying true to her mother.&amp;nbsp; There, I said it; it's true.&amp;nbsp; Over the last two years I have become increasingly resentful of Natalie's devotion to her mother; being of secondary concern is intolerable to me.&amp;nbsp; I think that at a certain point in my mind the following idea took shape:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I am not satisfied with the current state of affairs, but Natalie is. &lt;br /&gt;
Sex is our most powerful bond:&lt;br /&gt;
as long as I continue to perform sexually, Natalie will be satisfied with the current state of affairs;&lt;br /&gt;
her mother's needs will continue to be more important to her than mine.&lt;br /&gt;
If I cease to perform sexually, Natalie will be compelled to give my needs preference;&lt;br /&gt;
If Natalie shows exclusive concern with me and I reward her with sex, she will learn to be concerned with me, if not exclusively than primarily.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I am deeply disturbed by this: I feel that I am a very bad person, undeserving of good fortune for having this desire.&amp;nbsp; (It has also occurred to me that my intense need for care explains why so many of the girls I went out with were doctors or doctors-in-training)&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
But at the same time, I have attained a relationship precisely according to my own pyschological specifications.&amp;nbsp; I have got my own way in everything that is important to me.&amp;nbsp; Natalie is sexually available when I want her and I induce sufficient guilt in her to suppress her dissatisfaction when I do not want her; she defers to me as a matter of course; she does not bother me too much with her concerns; she refrains from discussing her involvement with her mother; she treats my happiness as an overriding concern.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For much of our relationship, I felt that Natalie did not want me to talk about my dissatisfaction, I felt that she only wanted to hear about good things.&amp;nbsp; I felt very neglected and lonely.&amp;nbsp; I have found that the only way to get through to her is to deprive her of sex; I don't have great faith in talking things through.&amp;nbsp; Recently it went better, but she reacted nastily to what I was trying to say until I attacked her own behaviour and made her feel poorly about herself.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I feel that we're both having a hard time of things and it's difficult for both of us to give anyone else the time of day.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I wish I could return to a simpler state of mind.&amp;nbsp; I am very unhappy that sex has become an instrument of control of mine.&amp;nbsp; I feel that we are no longer intimate.&amp;nbsp; Kisses and cuddles are perfunctory and mildly arousing, but her body is no longer exciting to me.&amp;nbsp; And it's not that I'm tired of her: she is still beautiful to me, but I am so stressed and resentful and scared of being neglected that I rarely relax around her, actually I am very rarely relaxed unless exhausted.&amp;nbsp; And by the time I wear myself out with other activities, I barely have any energy for sex.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
When Natalie signals her desire for sex, I become nervous and instinctively seek a distraction.&amp;nbsp; I don't want to come to bed straight away because then I'll have no excuse to do anything else, during which time her sexual desire might wane and thereby excuse me from the pressure of having to perform.&amp;nbsp; I am very rarely aroused.&amp;nbsp; And I don't know how to talk to her about it.</content>
    <blogger:created>2010-03-26T21:41:28.604Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2010-03-26T22:17:00Z</published>
    <updated>2010-03-26T22:17:48.414Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2010/03/low-libido.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-6380399819551683294.post-7565803613191072530</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>clockworksausage</name>
      <uri>http://www.clockworksausage.com</uri>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Market research for Clockwork PC</title>
    <content type='html'>OK, so I need to do market research for Clockwork PC, my fledgling computer business. &amp;nbsp;I have worked out the following business activities:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Selling:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;New computers with Linux&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Upgraded computers with Windows+Linux&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Upgraded computers with Linux&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Configuration:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Upgrading computers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Setting up computers to dual boot Windows+Linux or OSX+Linux&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Services:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Service calls&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computer repairs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data recovery + backup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data backup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Education:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Basics of Windows (one-on-one tuition)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basics of Linux (one-on-one tuition)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basics of Linux (classes)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to build your own computer (weekend workshop)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Now what am I supposed to find out in my market research?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Ultimately, I need to find out whether it's worthwhile to go into business at all. &amp;nbsp;That means I need to get a clear indication that:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
there is and will be a market for my business;&lt;br /&gt;
my prospective customers' willingness to pay is great enough for it to be worth my while;&lt;br /&gt;
my prices are within my prospective customers' range;&lt;br /&gt;
I have a competitive advantage.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
My business covers the following sectors:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Computer maintenance services&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span class="Apple-style-span" style="color: #444444; font-family: geneva,tahoma,Arial,Helvetica,sans-serif; font-size: 12px; line-height: 16px;"&gt;On and off site hardware maintenance of PCs and LANs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Computer and software retailing:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span class="Apple-style-span" style="color: #444444; font-family: geneva,tahoma,Arial,Helvetica,sans-serif; font-size: 12px; line-height: 16px;"&gt;Home computer equipment (including pre-packaged software)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span class="Apple-style-span" style="color: #444444; font-family: geneva,tahoma,Arial,Helvetica,sans-serif; font-size: 12px; line-height: 16px;"&gt;Computer software&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span class="Apple-style-span" style="color: #444444; font-family: geneva,tahoma,Arial,Helvetica,sans-serif; font-size: 12px; line-height: 16px;"&gt;Blank computer media&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Computer Consultancy:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span class="Apple-style-span" style="color: #444444; font-family: geneva,tahoma,Arial,Helvetica,sans-serif; font-size: 12px; line-height: 16px;"&gt;Hardware Consultancy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span class="Apple-style-span" style="color: #444444; font-family: geneva,tahoma,Arial,Helvetica,sans-serif; font-size: 12px; line-height: 16px;"&gt;Software Consultancy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span class="Apple-style-span" style="color: #444444; font-family: geneva,tahoma,Arial,Helvetica,sans-serif; font-size: 12px; line-height: 16px;"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Computer education and training:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span class="Apple-style-span" style="color: #444444; font-family: geneva,tahoma,Arial,Helvetica,sans-serif; font-size: 12px; line-height: 16px;"&gt;How to build your own computer (and how computers work)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span class="Apple-style-span" style="color: #444444; font-family: geneva,tahoma,Arial,Helvetica,sans-serif; font-size: 12px; line-height: 16px;"&gt;Basic computer use (Certificate I and II equivalents) in Windows and Linux&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
What do I know about my prospective customers?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Those who haven't got the know-how, or the time, or the inclination to investigate, fix parts, solve problems, replace parts, download applications or drivers, install or reinstall programs, build or configure or upgrade computers. (CBFs)&lt;br /&gt;
Those who are not attached to an application that cannot run comfortably in Wine. (Unattached)&lt;br /&gt;
Those who are interested in using Linux as a main operating system, but are not knowledgeable enough to configure it for themselves. (Linux Noobs)&lt;br /&gt;
Those looking to buy a computer who would prefer to buy from me. (Fans)&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
CBF:&lt;br /&gt;
These people will range across ages and demographics. &amp;nbsp;I'd have to conduct a lot of market research to narrow it down, but my guess is anyone who does not tinker with computers.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Unattached:&lt;br /&gt;
Dissatisfied with Windows, fearful of viruses, amenable to notions of freedom and economic empowerment, interested in an alternative operating system and applications, very keen on getting free stuff. &amp;nbsp;Could be small business owners, but probably more likely to be either the young and relatively inexperienced in computers or retirees interested in learning about it. &amp;nbsp;People who are very busy are unlikely to take to Linux unless they feel a great need for change. (How can I find out whether they feel a great need for change?)&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Linux Noobs:&lt;br /&gt;
Similar to the Unattached, may even be, but particularly disgruntled by Windows and especially attracted to Linux. &amp;nbsp;Very easy sale for me, great candidates for tuition and classes.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Fans:&lt;br /&gt;
Those looking to buy a computer amongst whom I have established a reputation for knowledge and trustworthiness. &amp;nbsp;Not sure what they want to get, don't want to spend too much money...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Computer retail: those who want value for money...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
A good starting point for defining my prospective customers is to consider my own journey into the IT world. &amp;nbsp;I have sufficient computing knowledge to feel very much at ease with computers and competently provide a number of computer-related services; however,&amp;nbsp;I refrain from calling myself a computer expert. &amp;nbsp;I have no formal training in computers or IT, and consider my greatest strengths be to interpersonal rather than technical. &amp;nbsp;I believe that anyone reasonably intelligent and sufficiently motivated could achieve my level of technical knowledge and proficiency without formal training, and those who are already comfortable with computers do not need my services and can purchase their own computers or computer parts for themselves. &amp;nbsp;My only advantage there is possibly greater experience or more regular access to computer parts, but I do not believe there is a profitable business in acting as a middleman for those wishing to buy computer parts.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Given my business activities, who would need me?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
My prospective customers can be classified according to few criteria:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Computer ownership - Looking to buy? Looking to upgrade?&lt;br /&gt;
Computer usage - Frequency? Applications? Comfort and familiarity?&lt;br /&gt;
Computer education -&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I'm trying to work out who really needs what I have to offer. &lt;br /&gt;
Someone looking to buy a computer for the first time, replace or upgrade an old one, or buy hardware or software;&lt;br /&gt;
Someone who has a problem with his computer;&lt;br /&gt;
Someone who is trying to do something new on the computer...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
hardware or software does not function satisfactorily, who wants to learn how to do something unfamiliar on the computer, whose configuration is unsatisfactory, who needs assistance or guidance with how something works on the computer;&lt;br /&gt;
A novice who is interested in computers and wants to further his knowledge.&lt;br /&gt;
Someone who is interested in opensource software and linux.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Computing requirements&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Therefore, a realistic starting point for prospective customers is to consider those who have no understanding of computers and those who can perform only basic computing functions. &amp;nbsp;As far as I can tell, proficiency in using computers does not correlate to number of years of usage, except in the obvious case of someone who has only started using a personal computer very recently.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Therefore, I guess that most of my business will come from the following;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
50+&lt;br /&gt;
Low education&lt;br /&gt;
Infrequent (less that daily) use of a computer&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In my personal experience I have noted that many people of retirement age have very limited understanding of computers, on account of the following:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cost. The perceived cost of purchasing and owning a computer is prohibitive to the many on a modest income, especially elderly immigrants. &amp;nbsp;I believe I can assemble a computer and install free opensource software at a price at a price far below that of a new computer from a major retailer. &amp;nbsp;However, I am up against very stiff competition in &lt;a href="http://www.greenpc.com.au/"&gt;GreenPC&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://computersforall.com.au/"&gt;computersforall.com.au&lt;/a&gt;: I cannot profitably match GreenPC's prices, nor can I match the convenience of weekly repayments or the economies of scale that computersforall offer. &amp;nbsp;In the case of selling refurbished computers, I have to differentiate myself not on price or convenience of payment, but on building up trust in a target population and offering greater customisation. &amp;nbsp;I noticed that both have very limited supplies and are out of stock in some cases -- that bodes well for me but also indicates the difficulty that established competitors have in sourcing their supplies. &amp;nbsp;I believe that with linux and opensource software I can offer greater customisation, which could be a point of difference, but I do not know whether there is interest in an alternative to Windows XP, pretty much the only OS being offered by my competitors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Language --&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lack of guidance --&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
So what do I know about my market structure?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Major Players:</content>
    <blogger:created>2010-02-10T05:18:59.209Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2010-02-10T21:56:00Z</published>
    <updated>2010-02-10T21:56:00.363Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2010/02/market-research-for-clockwork-pc.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-6380399819551683294.post-7620918941314045378</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>clockworksausage</name>
      <uri>http://www.clockworksausage.com</uri>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>A brief visit starts with a bang but ends on a frown</title>
    <content type='html'>&lt;span class="Apple-style-span" style="font-family: 'Lucida Grande'; font-size: x-large;"&gt;&lt;span class="Apple-style-span" style="font-size: 19px;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span class="Apple-style-span" style="font-family: 'Lucida Grande'; font-size: x-large;"&gt;&lt;span class="Apple-style-span" style="font-size: small;"&gt;She came over today. &amp;nbsp;I was busy and tired, but still happy to see her. &amp;nbsp;I'm not always happy to see her; she doesn't do anything to make me cross with her, but I sometimes feel that it's an effort to be happy around her. &amp;nbsp;I know I didn't always feel this way.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span class="Apple-style-span" style="font-size: small;"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span class="Apple-style-span" style="font-size: small;"&gt;We went out for dinner and I ate a bit too much. &amp;nbsp;I could have eaten in moderation, but the food was tasty and when she's around I become more self-indulgent. &amp;nbsp;I'm not blaming her though, that's just the way it seems to turn out.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span class="Apple-style-span" style="font-size: small;"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span class="Apple-style-span" style="font-size: small;"&gt;We came back and watched an episode of In Treatment in which Jake and Amy reach the point of wishing to divorce. &amp;nbsp;It was powerful and frightening and I felt the need to comfort her afterwards. &amp;nbsp;Later we went back to my room and made love had sex. &amp;nbsp;It didn't really feel like lovemaking, I simply felt aroused and comfortable with her in the safety of my room. &amp;nbsp;Afterwards when it was time for her to go already she went down on me, but I couldn't get hard. &amp;nbsp;That never used to be a problem for me. &amp;nbsp;I could say it's because I'm tired, but I know that's not true. &amp;nbsp;I haven't seen her in almost a week; had I really missed her I would have been aroused even under the influence. &amp;nbsp;The truth is that I was only pleased to see her, in more of a friendly and caring way, as if we are nothing more than old friends.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span class="Apple-style-span" style="font-size: small;"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span class="Apple-style-span" style="font-size: small;"&gt;Do I love her? &amp;nbsp;It's hard for me to say. &amp;nbsp;I think I love her, but I do feel differently about her these days. &amp;nbsp;Although I didn't really lose much today by seeing her for a couple of hours, I couldn't put my work out of my mind completely. &amp;nbsp;The issue is not that she takes me away from my work: she takes me away from the sense of control and security I derive from getting through tasks I deem important. &amp;nbsp;Especially towards the end of her visit today, I suppose it must have seemed that one moment I was smiling, aroused, energetic and within a few brief minutes I had become frowning, flacid, and tired.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span class="Apple-style-span" style="font-size: small;"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span class="Apple-style-span" style="font-size: small;"&gt;And she can see what's happening to me. &amp;nbsp;I try to hide it, but I can't. &amp;nbsp;I feel cowardly for doing so, but I'm trying to put on a brave face at the same time. &amp;nbsp;I should tell her how I really feel, but I'm not certain what I feel, and what it means.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span class="Apple-style-span" style="font-size: small;"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span class="Apple-style-span" style="font-size: small;"&gt;I imagine that this is the way it went with B. &amp;nbsp;At first they were young and passionate; then, as the futility of her situation become more and more apparent he tried everything he could to cope with it. &amp;nbsp;I doubt it was purely coincidental that he was offered a position in Sydney, or that it was impossible to return to Melbourne. &amp;nbsp;There was nothing really for him to come back to -- a lunatic father, an invalid mother, a useless family, and a daughter who could pull the plug on it but would destroy the core of her identity in doing so. &amp;nbsp;What could he do but stay at arm's length, concentrate on his work, and titillate himself with pornography. &amp;nbsp;I'm sliding down that slope as well, and I don't know how to stop it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span class="Apple-style-span" style="font-size: small;"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span class="Apple-style-span" style="font-size: small;"&gt;I wish I didn't feel so tired of her; I wish I could regain the hope, the optimism of our first days; I wish I could look at how far she's come, rather than at how far behind.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span class="Apple-style-span" style="font-size: small;"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span class="Apple-style-span" style="font-size: small;"&gt;I am afraid that if I break up with her I'd never truly get her back. &amp;nbsp;Perhaps we'd get back together, perhaps not; it wouldn't matter. &amp;nbsp;If I can't, if we can't work, if I can't work through this now while I'm still with her, then breaking up with her will always seem like a possibility when times get hard, which I expect they will. &amp;nbsp;And that's another problem: I foresee a difficult, draining life with her. &amp;nbsp;I wish I didn't, but my bent has always been to remove myself from difficult situations before I become embroiled in them. &amp;nbsp;I want life with her to be free of these destructive forces. &amp;nbsp;I want her to myself. &amp;nbsp;I want her to myself. &amp;nbsp;Or perhaps I don't want her anymore. &amp;nbsp;Do I? &amp;nbsp;Don't I? &amp;nbsp;I wish I knew.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <blogger:created>2010-02-04T11:15:33.419Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2010-02-04T11:44:00Z</published>
    <updated>2010-02-04T11:45:51.344Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2010/02/brief-visit-starts-with-bang-but-ends.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-6380399819551683294.post-7689550854044110658</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>aMapMapper</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Moving House</title>
    <content type='html'>&lt;span style="font-family: verdana;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: verdana;"&gt;As I sit here in my room, having recently returned from a sojourn of house sitting, a few things have occurred to me.

First, I really like sleeping in my own bed.  No offence to you and your beds, but after a while a bed becomes as personal as undies: even if the linen has been washed in a nuclear washing machine with industrial-strength detergent, it still has a residue of its usual occupant's soul.

Second, the best way to ensure that you never have too much stuff is to move house every once in a while.  Believe me, after schlepping your belongings from one place to another and back you'll become ruthless at throwing out the unnecessary.
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <blogger:created>2010-01-26T13:55:27.611Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2010-01-26T13:53:00Z</published>
    <updated>2010-01-26T13:59:31.458Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2010/01/moving-house.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-6380399819551683294.post-7876129843594943388</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>DRAFT</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>aMapMapper</name>
      <uri>http://www.clockworksausage.com</uri>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Conflation of Love and Stress</title>
    <content type='html'>I have come to realise that I no longer desire her.</content>
    <blogger:created>2010-02-02T13:10:28.248Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2010-02-02T13:09:00Z</published>
    <updated>2010-02-02T13:10:28.263Z</updated>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-6380399819551683294.post-8231183467687496586</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>clockworksausage</name>
      <uri>http://www.clockworksausage.com</uri>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Preparing To Dance</title>
    <content type='html'>The truth is that I'm unhappy with Natalie; I've been unhappy with Natalie for a while.&amp;nbsp; Part of my unhappiness is my current anxiety over the completion of my business plan, but it runs deeper than simply being very stressed about my work.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I do not really look forward to Natalie's visits as much as I used to.&amp;nbsp; At the same time, I think of her almost all the time, but most of my thoughts about her are worries and concerns.&amp;nbsp; I'm worried that the farm shop won't do well, I'm worried that she'll be assaulted on the train, I'm worried that something with her father might go wrong, I'm worried that any number of things completely beyond my control might happen that would bring my own life to a grinding halt.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I suppose right now Natalie wants nothing more than to get away from her delay worries, to be taken care of (she said so the other day), but to me that feels like a millstone around my neck.&amp;nbsp; She feels like a child that has to be constantly entertained or taken care of, a job that never ends.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I think I am overwhelmed by the enormity of her situation, and in order to cope with the terrible uncertainty of her life, that is our shared life, I conceive of her largely as a project to which I contribute.&amp;nbsp; I focus on the areas of her life where I can effect change and largely ignore the rest of it for fear of being drowned.&amp;nbsp; The problem is that I no longer conceive of her as Natalie herself, but rather as the physical manifestation of the financial and emotional burden that I now carry on her behalf.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I say I wish that Natalie and I could enjoy dancing together.&amp;nbsp; When we tried dancing, I found her a very unpleasant dance partner.&amp;nbsp; She seems to cling to me for dear life and to make every contact sexual.&amp;nbsp; I don't want our dancing to be sexual: it would put off other girls, with whom I want to dance, and it robs me of the enjoyment of moving to the music.&amp;nbsp; I enjoy dancing most when I become oblivious of my dance partner as a person, when she becomes an extension of my body, when I can immerse myself in music and forget about everything and everyboy else.&amp;nbsp; But when I dance with Natalie, she demands my attention, my cognition of her, and seems intolerant of my retreat into my own mind.&amp;nbsp; In my arms her frame feels very heavy or very loose, which makes it impossible for me to relax into the dance with her.&lt;br /&gt;
Why do I so want to dance with other girls?&lt;br /&gt;
Dancing with other girls is an escape from what Natalie has come to represent in my mind.&amp;nbsp; I am not interested in them sexually, and I say that because that is the first worry that comes to mind -- that I no longer desire Natalie -- but I am interested in them emotionally.&amp;nbsp; There are a few girls that find me very attractive, I assume, and are eager to dance with me.&amp;nbsp; When I dance with one of them I enjoy her attention because it does not demand my own; I can listen to and move with the music; I can enjoy the power of controlling her movements; and most importantly, I can retreat into my mind.&amp;nbsp; For the duration of a few songs I am free of all the worries, concerns, stresses, anxieties of my everyday life and especially of my life with Natalie.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I feel so terribly weighed down by my life with Natalie.&amp;nbsp; I so often wish that her mother would die quickly, suddenly, painlessly.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I fear that Natalie is a ticking time bomb.&amp;nbsp; Her mode of living is to care for others, to put others' concerns ahead of hers.&amp;nbsp; When she becomes very needy and clingy with me I believe I have a glimpse of Natalie after her mother's death.&amp;nbsp; I fear that when that day comes to pass Natalie's ambition in life will be to reclaim her lost childhood and she will no longer be the Natalie that provides me with the emotional support I crave, but one who craves my support even more strongly.&amp;nbsp; And when these thoughts come to me, I feel guilty, very guilty.&amp;nbsp; Because I feel that I am simply using Natalie, getting mileage out of her without certainty of sticking through the hard times, because these relatively easy times are already too tough for me.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I am bothered very much that I do not have the means to solve the great problems of Natalie's life because I measure the success of our relationship according to the improvement in her situation that I can effect.&amp;nbsp; For that reason I spend a lot of time and money on providing her with the best possible computer setup.&amp;nbsp; I am reassured by the knowledge that my equipping her technically assists her in notable, meaningful way.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
She isn't my girlfriend as much as she is my personal charity.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
But this is precisely what I began to seek many years ago: I always wanted a girl that would be absolutely devoted to me, whose life I could completely change, and I've finally got her.&amp;nbsp; But now that this fantasy of a girl who holds on to me, who looks up to me, is realized, I understand what that really means, and I don't want it anymore.&amp;nbsp; And besides, I simply don't believe that I deserve to be seen as someone pure and good.&amp;nbsp; It feels like a sham.&amp;nbsp; I find myself tempted to say things that would disappoint; I wonder what it would be like if I told her the truth about X, whether she would see me as I truly am.&amp;nbsp; What am I truly?&amp;nbsp; Not good enough.</content>
    <blogger:created>2010-03-04T21:58:37.361Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2010-03-05T01:17:00Z</published>
    <updated>2010-03-05T01:17:44.170Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2010/03/preparing-to-dance.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
</feed>