<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<feed xmlns='http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom' xmlns:blogger='http://schemas.google.com/blogger/2018'>
  <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-8207138652287083201</id>
  <title>I Am A Problem Solver</title>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-8207138652287083201.post-726340651869715087</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Alexander Garber</name>
      <uri>https://plus.google.com/+AlexanderGarber1984</uri>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Finding Work with an Arts Degree</title>
    <content type='html'>&lt;div class="separator" style="clear: both; text-align: center;"&gt;
&lt;a href="https://farm9.staticflickr.com/8473/8125991446_041f1c865d_b_d.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;"&gt;&lt;img border="0" height="213" src="https://farm9.staticflickr.com/8473/8125991446_041f1c865d_b_d.jpg" width="320" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div dir="ltr" id="docs-internal-guid-08798aad-1fca-49e8-7d9d-6633d7ceca2b" style="line-height: 1.15; margin-bottom: 0pt; margin-top: 0pt;"&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div dir="ltr" id="docs-internal-guid-08798aad-1fca-49e8-7d9d-6633d7ceca2b" style="line-height: 1.15; margin-bottom: 0pt; margin-top: 0pt;"&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div dir="ltr" id="docs-internal-guid-08798aad-1fca-49e8-7d9d-6633d7ceca2b" style="line-height: 1.15; margin-bottom: 0pt; margin-top: 0pt;"&gt;
&lt;span style="background-color: transparent; color: black; font-family: Arial; font-size: 15px; font-style: normal; font-variant: normal; font-weight: normal; text-decoration: none; vertical-align: baseline;"&gt;After the completion of my Arts degree at the University of Melbourne I faced the dizzying prospect of finding work with neither a specific qualification nor a clear career goal. &amp;nbsp;I assessed my skills and made it my mission to become a technical writer. &amp;nbsp;I focused my research of this profession on the most important people -- the employers. &amp;nbsp;I printed out every job advertisement I could find and compiled lists of recurring technical terms and acronyms; from there, I used all the resources at my disposal to piece together what these terms meant. &amp;nbsp;I attended meetings of the Australian Society for Technical Communication (Victoria) Inc (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.astcvic.org.au/" style="text-decoration: none;"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent; color: #1155cc; font-family: Arial; font-size: 15px; font-style: normal; font-variant: normal; font-weight: normal; text-decoration: underline; vertical-align: baseline;"&gt;www.astcvic.org.au/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent; color: black; font-family: Arial; font-size: 15px; font-style: normal; font-variant: normal; font-weight: normal; text-decoration: none; vertical-align: baseline;"&gt;), and spoke to all and sundry in order to puzzle out what employers were looking for in a technical writer.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div dir="ltr" style="line-height: 1.15; margin-bottom: 0pt; margin-top: 0pt;"&gt;
&lt;span style="background-color: transparent; color: black; font-family: Arial; font-size: 15px; font-style: normal; font-variant: normal; font-weight: normal; text-decoration: none; vertical-align: baseline;"&gt;Eventually, by virtue of focused research, autodidactic training, and numerous, energetic job applications, I got work as a technical writer and took the first major step in my work career.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent; color: black; font-family: Arial; font-size: 15px; font-style: normal; font-variant: normal; font-weight: normal; text-decoration: none; vertical-align: baseline;"&gt;Problem solved.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;</content>
    <blogger:created>2014-05-21T17:17:53.492Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2014-05-21T17:23:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2014-05-21T17:23:12.308Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2014/05/finding-work-with-arts-degree.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-8207138652287083201.post-2677252890773951112</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Alexander Garber</name>
      <uri>https://plus.google.com/+AlexanderGarber1984</uri>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>From Luddite To Technician</title>
    <content type='html'>&lt;div class="separator" style="clear: both; text-align: center;"&gt;
&lt;a href="http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-ywHbaOYblMY/U4togRisgvI/AAAAAAAADe4/UegVq_TBnuk/s1600/linux_desktop.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;"&gt;&lt;img border="0" src="http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-ywHbaOYblMY/U4togRisgvI/AAAAAAAADe4/UegVq_TBnuk/s1600/linux_desktop.jpg" height="200" width="320" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I am a problem solver, always have been, always will be.&amp;nbsp; Moreover, I belong to a special class of problem solvers -- those who can make a dysfunctional computer work again.&amp;nbsp; I use GNU/Linux; am comfortable on the command line; enjoy scripting, and derive pleasure from backing up data and installing an operating system.&amp;nbsp; In short, I am a fully fledged computer geek.&lt;br /&gt;
However, I used to anachronistic in my aversion from computers in favour of books, pen and paper.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In my mid-twenties I came across the philosophy of free and open source software, which inspired me to replace Windows with a Linux-based distribution, in spite of the risk and great cost of time and energy that this uninitiated transition entailed.&amp;nbsp; At the time, even the most user-friendly distributions were accompanied by various technical difficulties; in finding solutions and workarounds, I became intimately acquainted with computer hardware, drivers, system settings, etc.&lt;br /&gt;
Initially my approach was crude -- wipe out the whole system and start again, or resort to a cumbersome workaround, or do nothing and hope the problem would be solved by the next update.&lt;br /&gt;
As time went by, I learned to diagnose problems more accurately and ask the rights questions on forums; rather than uninstall an entire system or component, I learned to make subtle adjustments to the configuration files and settings; I learned to read computer code and terminal output; I learned to listen to what the machine was telling me.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This metamorphosis was gradual and incremental; a dramatic telling of the story would have me wake up one day with a veritable toolbox at my disposal, but the truth is far less spectacular and in my view far more absorbing.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
One of the most telling differences between a luddite and a technician is in their initial responses to an unexpected change.&amp;nbsp; I used to dread any and all changes, and discovering that a program had stopped working would evoke immediate frustration at a universe that had seemingly conspired against me.&amp;nbsp; It was as if there lurked just over my shoulder a shadowy gremlin who could disrupt my digital life on a whim.&lt;br /&gt;
As I worked through all manner of changes in layout and functionality on my open source odyssey, finding something unusual on screen -- or just a blank screen -- ceased to frighten me.&amp;nbsp; The sense of perennial foreboding came to be replaced by patience, curiosity, even excitement at the prospect of being the first to encounter and solve this problem.&amp;nbsp; I learned to run programs from the terminal so that I could follow the text output -- i.e. read what the program was telling the operating system -- and to make usefully detailed reports for the developers of the software; my mind got more and more used to working out how and why programs work well and don't.&amp;nbsp; The light of increasing knowledge and confidence dispelled the gremlins in my midst and showed them to be mere figments of my previously frustrated and fearful imagination.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This places me in a rare and privileged position.&amp;nbsp; Having joined the ranks of technicians relatively late in life, I see the trial and tribulations of the novice computer user and empathise with the frustrations of technicians who have long since overcome their fear of venturing into the unknown.&amp;nbsp; In my work as a technical writer and business owner, I served as bridge between these two emotional realities on behalf of scores of colleagues, customers, and clients.&amp;nbsp; The choice to radically overhaul my digital life, one of the greatest personal revolutions of our day, has enriched my life beyond measure, and has given me insight and power beyond my expectations.</content>
    <blogger:created>2014-05-30T07:29:55.086Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2014-06-01T08:56:00.002Z</published>
    <updated>2014-06-01T17:53:13.576Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2014/06/from-luddite-to-technician.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-8207138652287083201.post-3080960668620331737</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Alexander Garber</name>
      <uri>https://plus.google.com/+AlexanderGarber1984</uri>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Why It Is My Heart's Desire To Work in Alternative Dispute Resolution</title>
    <content type='html'>&lt;div class="separator" style="clear: both; text-align: center;"&gt;
&lt;a href="http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-Ycs_gST0czA/U4tQhckslLI/AAAAAAAADeo/vTN0XSxuKZg/s1600/legal.gif" imageanchor="1" style="margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;"&gt;&lt;img border="0" src="http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-Ycs_gST0czA/U4tQhckslLI/AAAAAAAADeo/vTN0XSxuKZg/s1600/legal.gif" height="213" width="320" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;"Why do you want to work in alternative dispute resolution?"&amp;nbsp;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I want to make a living by working in a profession that I would derive satisfaction from, that I am eminently suited to, and that accords with my values.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;"Why do you believe you would derive satisfaction from working alternative dispute resolution?"&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I enjoy helping people at a time of need, especially in a way that will ultimately save them time and money, with a view to fostering happier, more productive relations.&lt;i&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;"Why do you believe that you are eminently suited to working in alternative dispute resolution?"&lt;/i&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Success in ADR requires a host of attributes including inter alia wisdom, patience, problem-solving skills, active listening, negotiation technique, self-assurance, the ability to handle strong personalities, the ability to perform under pressure, impartiality, attention to detail, a strong command of language, tact, a keen ear, and powers of analysis.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I trust you will find me, to amply possess all of the above attributes and any relevant others.&amp;nbsp; Furthermore, I would delight in demonstrating to you my work ethic, willingness to learn, and examples of my auto-didactic accomplishments.&lt;i&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;"Why do you believe that working in alternative dispute resolution would accord with your values?"&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Two especially important philosophical principles in my life are the non-aggression principle and the sanctity of property rights.&amp;nbsp; By working in ADR I would contribute to the peaceful resolution of conflicts, and work towards fostering productive relationships between the parties.&amp;nbsp; Moreover, as an outspoken supporter of the free market, I am satisfied that in most cases the value proposition of at least one form ADR is superior; it naturally follows that I should like to sell and deliver the best product in the marketplace.</content>
    <blogger:created>2014-06-01T15:44:51.140Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2014-06-01T16:13:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-06-01T16:13:04.654Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2014/06/why-it-is-my-hearts-desire-to-work-in.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-8207138652287083201.post-3962190508859397268</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Alexander Garber</name>
      <uri>https://plus.google.com/+AlexanderGarber1984</uri>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>From Bookworm to Rugby Player</title>
    <content type='html'>&lt;div class="separator" style="clear: both; text-align: center;"&gt;
&lt;a href="https://farm4.staticflickr.com/3262/2308103774_339b88738d_z_d.jpg?zz=1" imageanchor="1" style="margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;"&gt;&lt;img border="0" height="279" src="https://farm4.staticflickr.com/3262/2308103774_339b88738d_z_d.jpg?zz=1" width="320" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="background-color: transparent; color: black; font-family: Arial; font-size: 15px; font-style: normal; font-variant: normal; font-weight: normal; text-decoration: none; vertical-align: baseline;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
I had always been clumsy, slow, and weak. &amp;nbsp;I tried my best at school sport and did some karate as a teenager, but no-one would have considered me, a skinny 21-year-old, a candidate for the contact sport of rugby.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Nevertheless, I went to my first training session at the University of Melbourne Rugby Club and soon discovered that I was one of the smallest players, with the worst fitness, the least physical strength, the poorest ball skills, the vaguest comprehension of the game, and, most embarrassingly of all, the slowest sprint -- I was even slower than the fat props. &amp;nbsp;There was not a single attribute in which I could distinguish myself.&lt;br /&gt;
Over the next few sessions, I considered how to approach this problem. &amp;nbsp;Everyone around me insisted that rugby was not a game for someone like me, but that made me more determined to make a good fist of it.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I listed the areas in which I would have to improve in order to be useful on the field:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: &amp;quot;Courier New&amp;quot;,Courier,monospace;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: black; font-size: 15px; vertical-align: baseline;"&gt;&lt;strike&gt;Size&lt;/strike&gt;&amp;nbsp;(Not going to grow any more)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: &amp;quot;Courier New&amp;quot;,Courier,monospace;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: black; font-size: 15px; vertical-align: baseline;"&gt;&lt;strike&gt;Power&lt;/strike&gt;&amp;nbsp;(No point in competing with the strong men)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: &amp;quot;Courier New&amp;quot;,Courier,monospace;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: black; font-size: 15px; vertical-align: baseline;"&gt;Fitness&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: &amp;quot;Courier New&amp;quot;,Courier,monospace;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: black; font-size: 15px; vertical-align: baseline;"&gt;Catching the ball&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: &amp;quot;Courier New&amp;quot;,Courier,monospace;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: black; font-size: 15px; text-decoration: none; vertical-align: baseline;"&gt;Passing the ball&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: &amp;quot;Courier New&amp;quot;,Courier,monospace;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: black; font-size: 15px; text-decoration: none; vertical-align: baseline;"&gt;Reading the game&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: &amp;quot;Courier New&amp;quot;,Courier,monospace;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: black; font-size: 15px; vertical-align: baseline;"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Speed&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: &amp;quot;Courier New&amp;quot;,Courier,monospace;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: black; font-size: 15px; vertical-align: baseline;"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Agility&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
I ruled out size and power outright; assumed that my fitness and ability to catch the ball would improve by simply attending every training session; and considered how I might get better at passing the ball, reading the game, sprinting faster and be more nimble.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
To get better at passing the ball, I bought a few cheap balls and went to the cricket nets. &amp;nbsp;I hung a boxing glove from the chicken wire at the end of the net and spent hours passing the ball the target.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
To get better at reading the game, I put together a booklet of diagrams of the rugby field, watched games on television and my team mates in action, and jotted in my book the formations on the field, distances, running angles, etc. &amp;nbsp;As time went by, I came to relate what happened on the field to my bird's eye diagrammatic view; eventually I learned the formations and developed an intuitive understanding of the layout.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Finally, to improve my speed and agility, I needed to learn how to sprint. &amp;nbsp;Now, I had never been a sprinter, and that doesn't mean I was a terrible sprinter: my body simply did not know how to sprint. &amp;nbsp;The best I could do was a heavy-footed high-knee jog in which my arms did one thing and my legs did another.&lt;br /&gt;
I went to the library and took out books on running; looked up running blogs online; tried to find videos of runners online; went to an athletics club and asked for help. &amp;nbsp;At first it seemed that I would never learn to run, but then I came across the concept of barefoot running.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The idea of running barefoot is that our feet are already eminently suited to running, if only we strengthen them by running on hard surfaces. &amp;nbsp;Over time, the muscles, bones, and ligaments will adapt to the stresses of running, and equally importantly, we will develop a light, efficient gait in order to reduce the impact on our feet. &amp;nbsp;It is well documented that African Olympic runners competed barefoot until the a couple of decades ago, including Zola Budd. &amp;nbsp;I mention Zola Budd, who is a white woman, because barefoot running in Western society is sometimes dismissed on ostensibly genetic grounds as being unsuitable for people of European descent; however, this argument is completely unfounded.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Every morning, I went to the local football oval, took off my shoes and started jogging around the field. &amp;nbsp;I had one simple rule: if it hurts my feet, I'm doing it wrong. &amp;nbsp;I can't say how long it took me to learn how to run barefoot, all I can say is that at first I shuffled, then jogged, then ran lightly, then ran at a comfortable pace, then galloped. &amp;nbsp;But all-out sprinting continued to evade me; I simply didn't know how to put it all together.&lt;br /&gt;
One night, as I ran with but a few distant street lights for illumination, I tried to sprint but felt heavy, and clumsy as usual; I slowed to a comfortable run and concentrated on my breathing. &amp;nbsp;Then, a marvellous thing happened: my entire body relaxed, I stood fully erect, felt the tension recede from my shoulders, and felt a faintly electric buzz as the final neural pathway between my arms and legs was forged. &amp;nbsp;I felt my arms and legs racing in perfect tandem, the wind blasted at my face, and it seemed as though a great invisible hand lay on my back and propelled me through space; my feet seemed to skim across the ground and the other side of the field suddenly seemed much closer. &amp;nbsp;I allowed my body to sustain this wonderful rhythm and felt myself zoom around the oval like a racehorse in full flight.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I had learned the secret of sprinting. &amp;nbsp;At the next training session's sprint training, instead of lagging with the portly front-rowers, I kept pace with the pack. &amp;nbsp;I don't know if anyone noticed it, but the difference was clear to me.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For the first season, I didn't even bother putting my hand up to play: I was a liability on the field. &amp;nbsp;I attended the games and recorded the goings-on in my trusty booklet of diagrams. &amp;nbsp;On Tuesdays and Thursdays, I ran as fast as my legs would carry me and launched myself bodily at every tackle bag.&lt;br /&gt;
During my morning barefoot runs, when the grass was frosty I rubbed my feet with Deep Heat to keep them warm -- they still went numb, but I persevered. &amp;nbsp;The area around the goals was muddy, so I practised sidestepping and swerving in the mud; I learned how to control my centre of gravity and accellerate when running on an arc.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
During the pre-season training for the second season, I kept on working on my four main areas:&lt;br /&gt;
Speed, agility, passing the ball, reading the game. &amp;nbsp;I watched hours of rugby matches on TV, took notes in my diagram booklet, and reviewed key passages for insight. &amp;nbsp;One day, during a warm-up game of touch rugby, I had the ball and instead of getting tunnel vision as had always happened to me, I noticed that a lot of players were bunched in front of me, including their right winger, who had come off his wing -- I looked out to my left and saw a team mate running along the side line, signalling for a long pass. &amp;nbsp;The ball spiralled from my hands, as it had so many times at the cricket nets, into his arms and he dashed passed the flat-footed defender on the wing. &amp;nbsp;It was an elementary move, but it was the first time I had processed real-time information in a game and applied this understanding in a meaningful way.&lt;br /&gt;
I had proved to myself that I have the capacity to read the game.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
During the second season, the coach was loathe to let me play. &amp;nbsp;I went to every game and paced the sideline, desperate to be given a chance, but the coach did not trust a small, skinny, clumsy nerd. &amp;nbsp;One day, when we barely put together a team on the day, a few of our players got injured in succession. &amp;nbsp;All the other substitutes were fielded. &amp;nbsp;Then another player of ours got hurt, and the coach despondently waved me on. &amp;nbsp;I rushed to my post on the left wing, far away from the action, but not much happened in my area.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Then a gigantic Pacific Islander got the ball and came rumbling down the field straight towards me. &amp;nbsp;I remembered my defence training, kept my eyes on his thighs, and just before he bowled me over, I dropped to my haunches and wrapped my arms around his legs. &amp;nbsp;His knees knocked together, and his enormous muscular frame fell like fleshy timber on top of me. &amp;nbsp;I rolled away, stood up, and joined in the ruck that had quickly formed around him.&lt;br /&gt;
I proved that I could tackle.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
A few games later, we were similarly low on numbers and I got my second chance. &amp;nbsp;Our inside centre was crabbing across the defence line; I saw a gap opening up; I ran towards the opening and called shrilly for the ball; my team mate passed the ball to me before he realised whom he had given it to. &amp;nbsp;The ball hung for a split-second in the air as my legs carried me towards it; my hands snatched it out of the air; and I felt the whoosh of that magical accelleration called sprinting. &amp;nbsp;Suddenly I was through the gap; no hands had grabbed me, I was in open space; the crisp air blasted my face; I heard heavy breaths on my nape. &amp;nbsp;I willed the tryline to come closer, but it was distant, oh so distant. &amp;nbsp;I waited to be pulled down, but no hands were on me. &amp;nbsp;I thought, "I don't care when I get tackled, I'm going to keep on running until someone stops me." &amp;nbsp;The tryline got closer and closer, and still I heard the heavy breathing and footsteps behind me. &amp;nbsp;"Why aren't I being tackled?" I thought. &amp;nbsp;"Maybe something is wrong; I don't care, I'm going to keep on running." &amp;nbsp;The tryline was tantalisingly close. &amp;nbsp;Just a few more steps, and there it was! I dived straight on to the land and felt the ball sink into my ribs -- not at all the way they did it on TV. &amp;nbsp;The footsteps ran past me. &amp;nbsp;I looked up and saw an opposing player walking with his hands on his hips. &amp;nbsp;I stood up and looked back, expecting the players to call me back, assuming that played had been stopped, but they were cheering. &amp;nbsp;"Where did that come from, mate? &amp;nbsp;Who taught you to run like that?" &amp;nbsp;They asked. &amp;nbsp;I tried to answer, but still needed to get my breath back. &amp;nbsp;It didn't matter though.&lt;br /&gt;
I proved that I could run.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Most of my rugby career was unremarkable. &amp;nbsp;Lots of running, lots of getting knocked over, lots of basic passes and shouting and sweating and rolling around in the mud. &amp;nbsp;But I made the transformation from a bookworm to a sportsman, and although I was never a player of note, my team mates came to see me as a competent, reliable player who ran hard and played bravely, and, every now and then, pulled out something special when it was needed.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Problem solved.</content>
    <blogger:created>2014-05-21T17:26:40.892Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2014-05-22T15:31:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-05-22T15:31:06.044Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2014/05/from-bookworm-to-rugby-player.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-8207138652287083201.post-5715294919915051075</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Alexander Garber</name>
      <uri>https://plus.google.com/+AlexanderGarber1984</uri>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Bullies at Highschool</title>
    <content type='html'>&lt;div class="separator" style="clear: both; text-align: center;"&gt;
&lt;a href="http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-mLZrkQyDZO8/U3zfh2nwAOI/AAAAAAAADdk/7MhYVqNY1PQ/s1600/8186440622_8f99bfa113_b.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;"&gt;&lt;img border="0" src="http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-mLZrkQyDZO8/U3zfh2nwAOI/AAAAAAAADdk/7MhYVqNY1PQ/s1600/8186440622_8f99bfa113_b.jpg" height="212" width="320" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div dir="ltr" id="docs-internal-guid-08798aad-1fc0-85f1-1ed4-f7a8d4ddbc9c" style="line-height: 1.15; margin-bottom: 0pt; margin-top: 0pt;"&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div dir="ltr" id="docs-internal-guid-08798aad-1fc0-85f1-1ed4-f7a8d4ddbc9c" style="line-height: 1.15; margin-bottom: 0pt; margin-top: 0pt;"&gt;
&lt;span style="background-color: transparent; color: black; font-family: Arial; font-size: 15px; font-style: normal; font-variant: normal; font-weight: normal; text-decoration: none; vertical-align: baseline;"&gt;When, as a young teenager I was bullied by thugs at my local government school, I took up Karate and learned enough to fight back. &amp;nbsp;I wouldn’t say that I defeated any of the larger, more powerful bullies, but I held my own. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I didn’t need to become a fearsome fighter, nor did I have to commit acts of criminal violence. &amp;nbsp;My goal was not to be bullied, which was accomplished as soon as they realised that I was not an easy target. &amp;nbsp;Moreover, my bravery won me the respect and protection of other boys in class, which elevated my status out of the lower ranks of the schoolboy pecking order.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent; color: black; font-family: Arial; font-size: 15px; font-style: normal; font-variant: normal; font-weight: normal; text-decoration: none; vertical-align: baseline;"&gt;Problem solved.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;</content>
    <blogger:created>2014-05-21T17:07:55.063Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2014-05-21T17:17:00.003Z</published>
    <updated>2014-05-21T17:17:29.591Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2014/05/bullies-at-highschool.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
</feed>