<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<feed xmlns='http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom' xmlns:blogger='http://schemas.google.com/blogger/2018'>
  <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5732700140968379816</id>
  <title>Evyatar's blog</title>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5732700140968379816.post-215014603533826159</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Semper Veritas</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Test</title>
    <content type='html'>Test</content>
    <blogger:created>2012-11-14T07:51:45.135Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2012-11-14T07:51:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2012-11-14T07:51:45.139Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2012/11/test.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5732700140968379816.post-820424333925950891</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Semper Veritas</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Tasks to complete before 28/11/2012</title>
    <content type='html'>&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Send an email to alexandergarber@gmail.com so that I can send you emails in the future to notify you of when I have marked your writing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add thecriticalgman@gmail.com as a reader of this blog so that I can add this blog to my feed reader.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn how to use Google Reader and add this blog to its feed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</content>
    <blogger:created>2012-11-15T08:26:39.909Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2012-11-15T08:28:00Z</published>
    <updated>2012-11-15T08:28:17.164Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2012/11/tasks-to-complete-before-28112012.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5732700140968379816.post-1469526048637179100</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Semper Veritas</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>REVIEW of Section A: Assignment: The Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night Time</title>
    <content type='html'>&lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;This dialogue contains all of the relevant information you need in order to answer the question by writing about an event in the novel from the perspective of Mr Boone.&amp;nbsp; Well done.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I understand why you gave the policeman those questions -- you needed Mr Boone to reply with the correct information.&amp;nbsp; However, how else could the policeman ask those questions without sounding as if he is accusing Mr Boone of doing something bad&lt;span style="color: black;"&gt;?&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; Policemen can't legally do that.&amp;nbsp; Try again, and imagine HOW you would ask those same questions in a neutral way.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;div class="character"&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="character"&gt;
MR. Boone&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="dialog"&gt;
Excuse me, officer; I'd like to report a missing child.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="character"&gt;
Policeman&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="dialog"&gt;
Alright, can you please describe the boy to me?&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="character"&gt;
MR.BOONE&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="dialog"&gt;
He has a rat in his pocket with its head sticking out, he is 13
years of age, and he would have wandered around in the station for a while
before taking the train.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="character"&gt;
POLICEMAN&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="dialog"&gt;
Hmm... okay, where was the child heading to? How would
you even know if he was here or not?&lt;span style="color: red;"&gt; (Is this how a policeman would speak? "How would you even know... ?" is what you say when you making an accusation)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="character"&gt;
MR.BOONE&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="dialog"&gt;
Early in the morning, I was going down to the kitchen to grab
&lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;(make?)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strike&gt;some&lt;/strike&gt; breakfast for me and for my child, and as I went down, I see a note on the
table saying that he was leaving to London, &lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;where his mother lives.&lt;/span&gt; he &lt;strike&gt;obviously had snuck out wrote me
a letter saying that he is going to see his mother,&lt;/strike&gt; He did not mention anything
about the train station, but &lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;it's &lt;/span&gt;the only way &lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;I imagine he could &lt;/span&gt;get to London from here&lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;u&gt;is
catching the trains in this train station.&lt;/u&gt; &lt;u&gt;Sir&lt;/u&gt;, &lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;Officer&lt;/span&gt;, I am very worried about his
safety, he has &lt;strike&gt;got autism&lt;/strike&gt; &lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;is autistic &lt;/span&gt;and he does not know the outside world, I need to get
to him as soon as possible!&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="character"&gt;
POLICEMAN&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="dialog"&gt;
Why did run out of the house sir? Did you do anything that bad
to cause him going all the way from London? &lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;(This sounds like an accusation)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="character"&gt;
MR.BOONE&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="dialog"&gt;
Well, I killed our family's dog and he got really mad with me
because he did not like people and he really liked his dog, he understood the
dog more than he understood people, I do not have any time constable, I need to
hurry up before he will be on his way to another city! I did not even imagine
how bad he would have reacted to this and would have actually do this to me, I
love him and I want him back safe.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="character"&gt;
POLICEMAN&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="dialog"&gt;
Sure thing, he escorted him to buy a ticket, and how to get on
the train to London, I know exactly who it is now... speaking of train tickets,
and do you have your train ticket on you?&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="character"&gt;
MR.BOONE&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="dialog"&gt;
Thank you very much for you assistance constable, I do not have
my ticket on me at the moment but I got some spare cash on me, after all he
took my credit card and he should have been stopped for doing that. You should
have also stopped him from trying to run away, he probably told you all about
how he wants to run away and how I am bad.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="character"&gt;
POLICEMAN&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="dialog"&gt;
No problem, but Why in the first place would he have gone to
London? &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="character"&gt;
MR.BOONE&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="dialog"&gt;
To see his mother of course, anyways I am going to go off to
the train, its coming in 2 minutes. If you see him around here again, please
keep him with you because I will come back and see if he has came back.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="character"&gt;
POLICEMAN&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="dialog"&gt;
Will do sir, I will let the other constables know about this.'&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="character"&gt;
MR.BOONE&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="dialog"&gt;
And again, thank you kindly constable, I really appreciate
that. &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="character"&gt;
POLICEMAN&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="dialog"&gt;
That's my job.&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    <blogger:created>2012-11-15T08:12:37.554Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2012-11-15T08:22:00Z</published>
    <updated>2012-11-15T08:22:00.861Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2012/11/review-of-section-assignment-curious.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5732700140968379816.post-2358176853855307888</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>Semper Veritas</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>REVIEW of Section B: Essay, The novel is about being different. </title>
    <content type='html'>&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;div class="MsoNormal"&gt;
&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16.0pt; line-height: 115%;"&gt;The
novel: "The curious incident of the dog at night time" is about
being different&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;
&lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;&lt;i&gt;GENERAL NOTES:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;Your essay satisfies the most important criterion: &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;it answers the question&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, so well done. Follow my comments to make the essay better.&amp;nbsp; I want to draw your attention to a couple of points diction and punctuation during our next lesson.&amp;nbsp; Otherwise, it's looking good.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;&lt;i&gt;****&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;You need to add an introduction.&amp;nbsp; It should look &lt;b&gt;like&lt;/b&gt; the following.&amp;nbsp; That means you should take this and re-write it in your own words.&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;&lt;i&gt;The novel "The Curious Incident of the Dog at Night Time" by (author) gives an account of what it means to be different.&amp;nbsp; It tells the story of a teenaged boy called Christopher, and the decisions he makes in response to disturbing incident reveal that although being "different" can be difficult, it is important to recognise how we are different from each other in order to better understand each other's perspective. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strike&gt;Christopher is obviously an exceptionally unusual person because of his 
autism. Extreme Autism is what Christopher has got, and its very rare, 
which makes him exceptionally an unusual type of different. He is 
different throughout the book at the cause of him not being able to 
socialize with people and being even more sociable with animals,&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strike&gt; &lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;First, establish that Christopher is "different"; then, point out that has things in common with other boys his age:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;&lt;i&gt;CHRISTOPHER IS DIFFERENT&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Christopher is most obviously different from his classmates in that he is autistic.&amp;nbsp; This means that&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt; he 
connects better with animals rather than humans, &lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;&lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt; he owns a pet rat. &lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;[Do the other boys think that keeping a rat as a pet is strange?]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Christopher &lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;&lt;i&gt;has an extreme dislike of being touched, and he even &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;hit a policeman for touching him, &lt;strike&gt;that is an unusual act 
that people at 15 of age (which is his age too) would not do&lt;/strike&gt;, he talks 
with too much&amp;nbsp;unnecessary detail and he speaks &lt;strike&gt;it&lt;/strike&gt; &lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;&lt;i&gt;very&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt; fast.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
He is 
exceptionally&amp;nbsp;&lt;strike&gt;intelligence&lt;/strike&gt; &lt;i&gt;&lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;intelligent&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;. He is able to calculate the volume of a 
police cell in &lt;i&gt;&lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;in a few &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;seconds &lt;strike&gt;with&lt;/strike&gt; &lt;i&gt;&lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;in&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt; his head &lt;strike&gt;only&lt;/strike&gt;, he always calculates the 
things around him and &lt;strike&gt;get&lt;/strike&gt; &lt;i&gt;&lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;gets the&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt; the right answers straight away, he likes to be 
organized by having a timetable that make him feel good when he knows 
what he is doing everyday.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;&lt;i&gt;CHRISTOPHER HAS THINGS IN COMMON WITH HIS CLASSMATES&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Although &lt;strike&gt;that&lt;/strike&gt; Christopher is &lt;strike&gt;a very different
 person from people&lt;/strike&gt; &lt;i&gt;&lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;certainly unusual&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt; &lt;strike&gt;he is also the same like other people, he had&lt;/strike&gt; &lt;i&gt;&lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;has&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt; a dog
 &lt;strike&gt;as his pet&lt;/strike&gt;, he has a normal family, he wants to be famous, he wants to 
be a&amp;nbsp;successful&amp;nbsp;person like&amp;nbsp;Sherlock&amp;nbsp;Holmes, &lt;strike&gt;&lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;(this is good, but the next few things show again he is different)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strike&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;&lt;i&gt;CHRISTOPHER IS DIFFERENT&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
he wants to achieve things,
 he even wrote a book, and get an 'A' grade on his subjects, he still 
had a friend and her name is Siobhan, she taught him how society works ,
 and how to react to it, although these are minor similarities with 
other people.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The&amp;nbsp;meaning of being different is being not alike in character, 
&amp;nbsp;Christopher does not know if he is sad or happy about being that 
different, although, the symptoms of Autism cause him to be sad and 
happy, he is happy that he can socialize with animals because they are 
more simpler to him than people that he talks to, being able to have his
 day like he wants it in a schedule, although he is sad because; he is 
unable to work out how being social works between different people from 
him and between him, he exceptionally does not like loud noises, he does
 not like being touched.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
If Christopher had a choice to not be Autistic, he wouldn't have known 
whats better for him which is another symptom caused by Autism, if he 
wanted to not be Autistic he would have done it for being social with 
people and&amp;nbsp;experiencing&amp;nbsp;new things.&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;In my &lt;strike&gt;humble&lt;/strike&gt; &lt;i&gt;&lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;(Do not say "in my humble opinion" unless you have a reason to use "humble")&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/i&gt;opinion, would say that being an Autistic person is 
negative and positive&lt;strike&gt;,&lt;/strike&gt;&lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strike&gt;in our age,&lt;/strike&gt; Autistic people are not as popular, 
not sociable, do not seem to have more than 1 to 2 friends and seems 
like everyone makes fun of them, they seem to get annoyed easily and are
 very delicate with everything you do with them, it is very hard to be 
Autistic, although,on the bright side being Autistic could mean that you
 are able to be someone like Stephen&amp;nbsp;Hawking, which he is also known for
 his gigantic amounts of knowledge, &lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;(Stephen Hawking is not autistic -- do a Google search for "famous autistic people")&lt;/span&gt;&lt;i&gt; &lt;/i&gt;Autism may cause you to have an 
amazing amount of memory, &lt;strike&gt;exceptionally intelligent&lt;/strike&gt; &lt;i&gt;&lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;exceptional intelligence&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;, got his own way of 
thinking which i would like to have too. &lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;(I don't understand what you mean by this last part)&lt;/span&gt; When I first came from Israel 
to Australia, I felt isolated from the people around here because I was 
very different from the people around here.&amp;nbsp; I didn't&amp;nbsp;like footy or 
cricket, but I was willing to try it out, I was &lt;strike&gt;too bad at it&lt;/strike&gt; &lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;&lt;i&gt;not very good at these sports / I didn't really enjoy these sports / I struggled to play these games well &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;and hoped I
 would mix with them.&amp;nbsp; &lt;span style="color: red;"&gt;(I don't understand what you mean by "mix with them")&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In the end, I learned how to mix with people that I
 want to mix with pretty well, everything takes time.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
By: Evya Mati</content>
    <blogger:created>2012-11-15T07:36:13.349Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2012-11-15T08:09:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2012-11-15T08:11:57.857Z</updated>
    <blogger:filename>/2012/11/review-of-section-b-essay-novel-is.html</blogger:filename>
  </entry>
</feed>